<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?>
<UnitTypes>
	<UnitType InternalName="Golem_Cosinivatha">
		<CreatureType>Champion</CreatureType>
		<GameModifier>
			<ModType>Resource</ModType>
			<Attribute>Unrest</Attribute>
			<Value>-5</Value>
			<Provides>-5% Unrest in the city this unit is in</Provides>
		</GameModifier>

		<DisplayName>Ruby</DisplayName>
		<Backstory>Ruby was once a White Golem nearly identical to the rest of her kind.  Not long after Lochean began assembling the remainder of the White Golems to begin their empire, Ruby was sent as an emissary to a sorceress reputed to have extensive knowledge of golems.  When Ruby arrived, she discovered that this was indeed the case.  The sorceress had a wide array of golems who were serving in various capacities in her tower.  While Ruby noted this for later action when a task force could be spared for their recovery, her primary mission was to negotiate for transfer of knowledge, and she quickly set about her task.  It proved difficult, however, to keep the sorceress focused on the negotiations.  In addition to the normal biological functions such as eating and sleeping that she knew to expect, the sorceress would also frequently leave to observe some natural phenomena, such as small bird-animals resupplying their energy by feeding at plants in the garden, or the light patterns on clouds when the day period was ending.  It was exceedingly hard to predict and even harder for her to understand.  When she asked the other golems about it, they either ignored her or gave illogical answers of the kind one might expect from a mortal.

Realizing that she was not accomplishing her task, Ruby decided to speak to the sorceress about the matter so that they could proceed.  She asked the sorceress to explain the nature and reason behind the deviations, so that she could anticipate them and plan for more efficient use of her time. The sorceress agreed, though she said that the process may take longer than Ruby anticipated, and that the outcome might not be what she expected.  Ruby considered, and decided that the risk was negligible, while the potential benefits of obtaining the knowledge were great, as were the consequences of failure if she returned without the information.  She agreed.  The sorceress smiled, took hold of Ruby's hands, and led her outside to begin her education.  

It did indeed take longer than Ruby had anticipated, and when the sorceress had finished explaining, some months had passed.  Ruby found that she no longer cared to return to the other golems with the information; it would be of no use to them.  She understood what the other golems in the sorceress' residence were doing there; they were not slaves, but rather had found a tutor for knowledge that no one else could or would teach.  The sorceress' power over golems was skill in empathy and a gift for instruction, not special magical knowledge.  Furthermore, she had come to appreciate beauty in the world.  Especially the color red.  In fact, she had so much come to appreciate the color red that she took a new name after a stone with that color.  

For all this, though, she was not willing to stay with the sorceress indefinitely.  She found that she did not appreciate the same things, that she had her own sense of taste and style.  She determined that she would see what other beauty the world had to offer, and that she would acquire the means to collect what she desired.  She knew that she would be able to employ her capabilities to earn gildar, with which she could purchase beautiful things from others.  Or she could take them by force should she obtain a position of power over them.  She also understood that this would not be as easy among her own kind, who do not appreciate beauty in the way she does now.  Therefore, she would set out on her own.

Before she left, she asked a boon of the sorceress; she wished to be as red as her namesake.  The sorceress granted her wish, and today Ruby is still bright red, as you can see.</Backstory>

		<ModelPath>ef_golem_body.hkb</ModelPath>
		<SkeletonPath>Gfx\HKB\Units\K_Male_Skeleton_01.hkb</SkeletonPath>
		<EyeTexture>gfx\Eyes\blinks\Eyeblink_F4_Blk.png</EyeTexture>
		<AnimationPack>EF_NoblemanAnimationPack</AnimationPack>

		<ShowAsSingleUnit>false</ShowAsSingleUnit>
		<CutSceneDataPack>DefaultUnitCutscenePack</CutSceneDataPack>
		<ModelScale>1.0000</ModelScale>
		<TacticalModelScale>1.5000</TacticalModelScale>
		<EquipmentScale>1.0000</EquipmentScale>
		<ClothMapScale>1.6</ClothMapScale>
		<BattleAnimationBehavior>Melee</BattleAnimationBehavior>
		<MovementType>land</MovementType>
		<BobbingFrequency>0.0000</BobbingFrequency>

		<ClothPoseIndex>7</ClothPoseIndex>
		<InfoCardBackground>BG33_HillPlains</InfoCardBackground>
		<InfoCardBackgroundFlipped>1</InfoCardBackgroundFlipped>

		<CanBeDesigned>0</CanBeDesigned>    
		<Allegiance>Empire</Allegiance>
		<Unique>1</Unique>
		<IsNPC>1</IsNPC>
		<NPCSpawnLikelihood>100</NPCSpawnLikelihood>
		<IsChampion>1</IsChampion>
		<SoundPack>SoundPack_Generic_Female</SoundPack>
		<Gender>Female</Gender>

		<SpawnRating>3</SpawnRating>
		<Quote>Did you know that people are a beautiful red color inside?</Quote>
		<NPCRecruitmentText>%d gildar would let me purchase more red things.</NPCRecruitmentText>

		<SelectedAbilityBonusOption>Blood_Golem</SelectedAbilityBonusOption>
		<SelectedAbilityBonusOption>PathOfTheMage</SelectedAbilityBonusOption>
		<SelectedAbilityBonusOption>Golem_Trait_Selfrepair</SelectedAbilityBonusOption>
		<SelectedAbilityBonusOption>Fire1</SelectedAbilityBonusOption>
		<SelectedAbilityBonusOption>Tinker</SelectedAbilityBonusOption>
		
		<Medallions InternalName=""/>
		<WageOverride>1</WageOverride>
		<MovingSFX>TEMP_KnightMarching1</MovingSFX>
		<LevelMilestone InternalName="L1">
			<Level>1</Level>
			<UnitStat_Accuracy>80</UnitStat_Accuracy>
			<UnitStat_BG_IsConstruct>1.0000</UnitStat_BG_IsConstruct>
			<UnitStat_BG_IsEmpire>1.0000</UnitStat_BG_IsEmpire>
			<UnitStat_BG_IsHumanoid>1.0000</UnitStat_BG_IsHumanoid>
			<UnitStat_BG_IsNotAlive>1.0000</UnitStat_BG_IsNotAlive>
			<UnitStat_BG_IsRace_Golem>1.0000</UnitStat_BG_IsRace_Golem>
			<UnitStat_BG_IsChampion>1.0000</UnitStat_BG_IsChampion>
			<UnitStat_CombatSpeed>22.0000</UnitStat_CombatSpeed>
			<UnitStat_HitPoints>20.0000</UnitStat_HitPoints>
			<UnitStat_ChanceToCrit>1</UnitStat_ChanceToCrit>
		</LevelMilestone>

		<AutoCreateEquipment>Dagger</AutoCreateEquipment>
		<AutoCreateEquipment>RingOfEmbers</AutoCreateEquipment>

		<Color_Skin>227,41,41,255</Color_Skin>
		<Color_Hair>107,15,15,255</Color_Hair>
		<Color_Clothing1>200,0,50,255</Color_Clothing1>
		<Color_Clothing2>107,15,15,255</Color_Clothing2>
		<Color_Metal>255,255,255,255</Color_Metal>
		<Texture_Skin>M_Golem_Texture_01.png</Texture_Skin>

		<UnitModelType>Golem</UnitModelType>
		<NPCFreeRecruit>0</NPCFreeRecruit>
		<RaceType>Race_Type_Golem</RaceType>
		<OnHitParticleName>Bloody_OnHit</OnHitParticleName>
	</UnitType>

</UnitTypes>
