<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<!--Children of Storm by Heavenfall-->
<!--XtraDeconstruct 3.0 by Primal-->
<RaceConfigs>
	<RaceConfig InternalName="KingdomofAngel">
		<DisplayName>Angels #K</DisplayName>
		<Description>The Angels were once servants of their God, but were cast out as they failed to prevent the Cataclysm. Now, having lost the ability to fly, they seek to return to the grace of their God.
		
		The Angels were a divine race, granted the utmost love and compassion of their god, whom they lived with at the Mountain of the Gods. They spent their days pondering philosophical quandaries and praying to their lord, and playing different games that required them to fly around. When the Titans arrived to the Elemental world, the Angels were sent as agents of a higher power to influence the turn of events against the Titans. Their god gave them this task to keep magic flowing freely in the world. However, the Angels failed their god twice. First, the Titans managed to capture the magic in the shards, and second, the world was destroyed in the Cataclysm. Their god blamed the Angels for both these events, and so, the Angels were cast out from the Mountain of the Gods, no longer in their god's grace. The Angels lost the ability to fly, their wings now useless without the guiding hand of their god.
		
		Despite being so abandoned by their god, the current Angel society is fiercely fanatical. Rather than turn on their god for his betrayal, they believe that the Angels can work their way back into the god's good grace and then return to the Mountain of the Gods. But far from remaining the same society that they had before the Cataclysm, the Angels have undergone a great change in recent years. Their leader, the Angel of Hope, Colopatiron, has learned how to acess the magic stored in the shards, and now uses it to empower the Angel race much like their god used to do before. When this was discovered, there was a schism in their religion that quickly transformed it in its entirety. They now call this progress the "New Faith". Profoundly magical in their essence, they have taken to using shards like no other race ever has or ever will on the face of the Elemental world.  Despite this, not a single Angel has to this day mentioned the possibility that perhaps they do not need their god.</Description>
		<LorebookIntroText/>
		<AIPersonality>AI_General</AIPersonality>
		<Capital>Hinoqua</Capital>
		<City>Niold</City>
		<City>Pheyl</City>
		<City>Issay</City>
		<City>Souh</City>
		<City>Makas</City>
		<City>Snakebane</City>
		<City>Slaiss</City>
		<City>Optera</City>
		<City>Ley'den</City>
		<ShortName>Angels</ShortName>
		<LeaderName>Colopatiron</LeaderName>
		<PopulaceName>Angels</PopulaceName>
		<Alignment>Good</Alignment>
		<FactionAllegiance>Kingdom</FactionAllegiance>
		<SelAbilityBonusOption>MasterworkChain</SelAbilityBonusOption>
		<SelAbilityBonusOption>Player_X_Angels</SelAbilityBonusOption>
		<SelAbilityBonusOption>Rivermod_Golem2</SelAbilityBonusOption>
		<SelAbilityBonusOption>BloodOfTheRedeemer</SelAbilityBonusOption>
		<SelAbilityBonusOption>Ability_X_Deorcnysse1000</SelAbilityBonusOption>
		<MusicTheme>WanderersHome</MusicTheme>
		<DefaultCityWallSet>CityWalls_Fence</DefaultCityWallSet>
		<NewCityHubType>CityHub1</NewCityHubType>
		<CapitalHubType>CityHub1</CapitalHubType>
		<RaceClassification>Angel</RaceClassification>
		<RaceDisplayName>Angels</RaceDisplayName>
		<RaceInternalName>Race_Type_Angel</RaceInternalName>
		<GenericUnitType_Male>Generic_Angel_Male</GenericUnitType_Male>
		<GenericUnitType_Female>Generic_Angel_Female</GenericUnitType_Female>
		<TraderUnitType>TraderTest</TraderUnitType>
		<ShopkeeperUnitType>Shopkeeper_Angel</ShopkeeperUnitType>
		<ChooseFactionBack>Faction_Background_Altar.png</ChooseFactionBack>
		<UnitScale>1</UnitScale>
		<UnitSkinColor>215,150,100</UnitSkinColor>
		<UnitHairColor>155,110,75</UnitHairColor>
		<UnitClothing1Color>220,220,220,255</UnitClothing1Color>
		<UnitClothing2Color>100,100,100</UnitClothing2Color>
		<UnitMetalColor>255,255,255</UnitMetalColor>
		<BuildingPrimaryColor>200,200,200</BuildingPrimaryColor>
		<BuildingSecondaryColor>79,48,20</BuildingSecondaryColor>
		<BuildingRoofColor>30,84,48</BuildingRoofColor>
		<ZoneOfControlColor>255,255,255</ZoneOfControlColor>
		<BuildingStyle>KingdomStyle</BuildingStyle>
		<TechTree>TechTree_X_Angels</TechTree>
		<EnvironmentTerrainType>2</EnvironmentTerrainType>
		<NonBuildableEnvironmentType>DeadEnvironment</NonBuildableEnvironmentType>
		<PreferredLogoType>angelscrest</PreferredLogoType>
		<SovereignUnitType>Sovereign_Colopatiron</SovereignUnitType>
	</RaceConfig>
	<RaceConfig InternalName="KingdomofCentaur">
		<DisplayName>Centaurs #K</DisplayName>
		<Description>Centaurs, half horse, half men, were nomads before the Cataclysm, inhabiting a great plain called the Expanse. It was destroyed during the Cataclysm and they were forced to break their ancient traditions to survive.
		
		Before the Cataclysm, the Centaurs lived in a vast steppe called the Expanse. There, the "People" as they called themselves, roamed across the open land, herding great herds of cattle. The Centaurs were divided into several hundred Clans. These Clans fought each other for supremacy over the Expanse but rarely ventured beyond its limits. With no stone or wood to build cities with and bound by traditions crucial to the centaur life, they never managed anything the other species of the Elemental world would call a "civilization".
		
		The Centaurs were not only shaped by their traditions and the scarcity of resources in the Expanse  but also by the great thunderstorms that rolled across it. With no buildings to take shelter in, they relied first on scouts to inform the clans of impending storms. As they evolved into using magic, their reliance shifted to their shamans' ability to redirect the storms away from their herds.
		
		The Centaurs were mostly left alone by other races for two reasons. Primarily, the Expanse would not support any other lifestyle than the nomad one adopted by the Centaurs. Even if parts of the steppe were suitable for use in farming, the constant thunderstorms ruined any crops. Secondly, whenever a force would invade the Expanse, the Centaur clans united into a single force to drive the invaders out. Though torn apart by internal strife, the Centaur Clans were bound by tradition to fight side by side if their land came under threat. Their mobility ensured victory in the steppe, Centaurs being both faster and better suited for survival. Invaders were drawn into wars of attrition and eventually annihilated. At the height of their prosperity, the Centaurs could field an army of well over a hundred thousand men.
		
		At the same time, their tradition dictated that they not leave the Expanse and on the rare occasion that they did so, the individual Clans were easily repelled when their mobility and mastery of the land was no longer guaranteed.
		
		The Centaurs were struck by the Cataclysm more harshly than perhaps any other race. Following the end of the world, the entire Expanse was turned into a desert. Within a year, the Centaurs were almost completely killed off by starvation and the few clans that tried to leave the Expanse had no more success than they had before the Cataclysm. More than 90% of the Centaurs had perished a year after the Cataclysm but more was to follow. Unable to sustain any life, the changing Expanse prompted great change in the Centaur culture. Bound by the iron chains of tradition, they believed that they were meant to stay in the Expanse and that the fittest would survive. 
		
		A Centaur named Vini eventually challenged the ruling hierarchy of the Clans. A civil war erupted between the traditionalists that wanted to remain in the Expanse and the separatist faction led by Vini that wanted to leave the area in a single force powerful enough to not be repelled by the bordering inhabitants. Unlike previously in Centaur history, in this war the Clans were also prone to infighting as each Centaur had to decide for themselves what the appropriate thing to do was. Vini's faction was eventually victorious, but at great cost of life. By the time they had successfully escaped the desert lands of the Expanse, less than one in one hundred of the Centaurs were alive than had been before the Cataclysm. Now, Vini leads a haphazard collection of Clans with different traditions and motivations and rulers. Their old rules broken by changing circumstances, they are eager to take their places amongst the other Kingdoms to forge their own fate in the world. </Description>
		<LorebookIntroText/>
		<AIPersonality>AI_General</AIPersonality>
		<Capital>Hearth</Capital>
		<City>Burm</City>
		<City>Kaln</City>
		<City>Aone</City>
		<City>Aldu</City>
		<City>Aeny</City>
		<City>Duil</City>
		<City>Engre</City>
		<City>Chruiss</City>
		<City>Oughs</City>
		<ShortName>Centaurs</ShortName>
		<LeaderName>Vini</LeaderName>
		<PopulaceName>Centaurs</PopulaceName>
		<Alignment>Good</Alignment>
		<FactionAllegiance>Kingdom</FactionAllegiance>
		<SelAbilityBonusOption>Player_X_Centaurs</SelAbilityBonusOption>
		<SelAbilityBonusOption>Player_X_Centaurs_Faction</SelAbilityBonusOption>
		<SelAbilityBonusOption>Ability_X_Deorcnysse1000</SelAbilityBonusOption>
		<MusicTheme>WanderersHome</MusicTheme>
		<DefaultCityWallSet>CityWalls_Fence</DefaultCityWallSet>
		<NewCityHubType>CityHub1</NewCityHubType>
		<CapitalHubType>CityHub1</CapitalHubType>
		<RaceClassification>Centaur</RaceClassification>
		<RaceDisplayName>Centaurs</RaceDisplayName>
		<RaceInternalName>Race_Type_Centaur</RaceInternalName>
		<GenericUnitType_Male>Generic_Centaur_Male</GenericUnitType_Male>
		<GenericUnitType_Female>Generic_Centaur_Female</GenericUnitType_Female>
		<TraderUnitType>TraderTest</TraderUnitType>
		<ShopkeeperUnitType>Shopkeeper_Centaur</ShopkeeperUnitType>
		<ChooseFactionBack>Faction_Background_Altar.png</ChooseFactionBack>
		<UnitScale>1</UnitScale>
		<UnitSkinColor>70,50,35</UnitSkinColor>
		<UnitHairColor>155,110,75</UnitHairColor>
		<UnitClothing1Color>120,25,20,255</UnitClothing1Color>
		<UnitClothing2Color>78,60,55,255</UnitClothing2Color>
		<UnitMetalColor>255,255,255</UnitMetalColor>
		<BuildingPrimaryColor>165,145,130</BuildingPrimaryColor>
		<BuildingSecondaryColor>75,60,50</BuildingSecondaryColor>
		<BuildingRoofColor>90,15,10</BuildingRoofColor>
		<ZoneOfControlColor>255,255,155</ZoneOfControlColor>
		<BuildingStyle>KingdomStyle</BuildingStyle>
		<TechTree>TechTree_X_Centaurs</TechTree>
		<EnvironmentTerrainType>2</EnvironmentTerrainType>
		<NonBuildableEnvironmentType>DeadEnvironment</NonBuildableEnvironmentType>
		<PreferredLogoType>GenericCrest25</PreferredLogoType>
		<SovereignUnitType>Vini</SovereignUnitType>
	</RaceConfig>
	<RaceConfig InternalName="KingdomofDwarves">
		<DisplayName>Gnomes #K</DisplayName>
		<Description>Gnomes are master craftsmen, far more so than any other race. They are short and often bearded, although other than size their bodies are similar to those of the humans. Some believe the Gnomes to be humans who have evolved into smaller beings, as a result of spending generations underground digging in mines, although it is unwise to make such a claim to the face of a Gnome.
		
		Rather than land, the Gnomes favor underground fortresses, linked with cave systems where they ensure a water supply, an air supply and food supply without the requirements that the "surface dwellers" have, such as sunlight or arable land. These fortresses are raised and constantly expanded, as each Gnome must spend at least ten years of his or her life serving the fortress before entering adulthood. Within these vast fortresses, the Gnomes not only go about trying to survive, but they also spend their lives trying to become better craftsmen in various areas, such as metalworking or stonework (as they call those who work with crystals). Living up to 400 years before they perish, their craftsmanship is honed to perfection and armor or weapons crafted by them have no equal amongst the other races. Because of their underground cave systems, they are also ensured a fairly steady supply of crystals.
		
		The Gnome society is a mix of feudalism and democracy, with a Low King at the very top of the hierarchy. The Low King dictates who is to control various fortresses by appointing barons to rule them. Meanwhile, the Low King is himself (or herself) elected through a public vote where all Gnomes of adulthood participate and the Low King sits on the throne until dead. 
		
		Given their ability to thrive without access to surface resources, one would imagine that the Gnomes would have been fairly successful at establishing a power base before the Cataclysm. The Gnomes, sadly, have a tendency to get drawn into lengthy wars, not to mention their fortresses that constantly come under attack, particularly from the Greenskin. The reason the Gnomes get involved in such lengthy conflicts is mainly because of the fundamental pillar in Gnome culture: honor. After every battle, each slight to a Gnome's honor is written down and stored in great tomes. These tomes, called Grudgebooks, are held inside the fortresses of the Gnomes and it is the duty of all members of the hold to ensure that the grudges are "cleared", by bringing the offender to "justice". Of course, all conflicts merely add more grudges, and thus the Gnomes are locked by their honor in an ever-increasing spiral of violence and death.
		
		The Gnomes caught somewhat of a break during the Cataclysm, even though practically all of their fortresses were destroyed by shifting earth. The Gnomes themselves were at the time occupied with raids on nearby Goblin settlements and thus above ground. With the loss of their fortresses, so too were their Grudgebooks destroyed. This led to long discussions held by the surviving Gnomes. The fact that the grudges were written down ensured their authenticity. Did this mean that without the books the Gnomes were now honorless? Or was it, as others claimed, that the many small grudges had simply been replaced by the greatest grudge of all - a grudge against those who caused the Cataclysm? Regardless of what the elders argued, the fact is that the Gnomes came away from the Cataclysm relatively unscathed and had time to rebuild a few fortresses before the other races realized their weakness when not defending their keeps. In addition, the Gnomes had by luck managed to save their most important resource of all - the skill of the gnomish smiths and stoneworkers.</Description>
		<AIPersonality>AI_General</AIPersonality>
		<Capital>Belegost</Capital>
		<City>Nogrod</City>
		<City>Estolad</City>
		<City>Ashrad</City>
		<City>Amonrudh</City>
		<City>Eithel</City>
		<City>Nimras</City>
		<City>Khazad-Kar</City>
		<City>Aglon</City>
		<City>Erir</City>
		<ShortName>Gnomes</ShortName>
		<LeaderName>Nimgofl</LeaderName>
		<PopulaceName>Dwarves</PopulaceName>
		<Alignment>Good</Alignment>
		<FactionAllegiance>Kingdom</FactionAllegiance>
		<SelAbilityBonusOption>Dwarf_GreatFortresses</SelAbilityBonusOption>
		<SelAbilityBonusOption>GreatHammers</SelAbilityBonusOption>
		<SelAbilityBonusOption>LightPlate</SelAbilityBonusOption>
		<SelAbilityBonusOption>Rivermod_DwarfMagma</SelAbilityBonusOption>
		<SelAbilityBonusOption>Rivermod_Golem2</SelAbilityBonusOption>
		<SelAbilityBonusOption>Ability_X_Deorcnysse1000</SelAbilityBonusOption>
		<MusicTheme>WanderersHome</MusicTheme>
		<DefaultCityWallSet>CityWalls_Advanced</DefaultCityWallSet>
		<NewCityHubType>CityHub1</NewCityHubType>
		<CapitalHubType>CityHub1</CapitalHubType>
		<RaceClassification>Dwarves</RaceClassification>
		<RaceDisplayName>Dwarvess</RaceDisplayName>
		<RaceInternalName>Race_Type_Dwarves</RaceInternalName>
		<GenericUnitType_Male>Generic_Dwarves_Male</GenericUnitType_Male>
		<GenericUnitType_Female>Generic_Dwarves_Female</GenericUnitType_Female>
		<TraderUnitType>TraderTest</TraderUnitType>
		<ShopkeeperUnitType>Shopkeeper_Dwarves</ShopkeeperUnitType>
		<ChooseFactionBack>Faction_Background_Altar.png</ChooseFactionBack>
		<UnitScale>0.6</UnitScale>
		<UnitSkinColor>215,150,100</UnitSkinColor>
		<UnitHairColor>78,49,20</UnitHairColor>
		<UnitClothing1Color>78,49,20</UnitClothing1Color>
		<UnitClothing2Color>0,0,0</UnitClothing2Color>
		<UnitMetalColor>56,33,10</UnitMetalColor>
		<BuildingPrimaryColor>78,49,20</BuildingPrimaryColor>
		<BuildingSecondaryColor>79,48,20</BuildingSecondaryColor>
		<BuildingRoofColor>78,49,20</BuildingRoofColor>
		<ZoneOfControlColor>99,66,30</ZoneOfControlColor>
		<BuildingStyle>KingdomStyle</BuildingStyle>
		<TechTree>TechTree_X_Gnomes</TechTree>
		<EnvironmentTerrainType>2</EnvironmentTerrainType>
		<NonBuildableEnvironmentType>DeadEnvironment</NonBuildableEnvironmentType>
		<PreferredLogoType>gnomelogo</PreferredLogoType>
		<SovereignUnitType>Sovereign_Nimgofl</SovereignUnitType>
	</RaceConfig>
	<RaceConfig InternalName="KingdomofElves">
		<DisplayName>Elves #K</DisplayName>
		<Description>Elves are immortal magicians that subsisted in forests before the Cataclysm. Now they make a grab for power to prevent it happening again.
		
		Elves have existed in the Elemental world even before humanity. They have played practically no part in the history of the world, however. The Elves kept to the forest, where they  lived out their lives surviving on whatever the forests provide for them. On occasion, the Elves banded together to fight off those who wished to destroy their forests  but mostly this resulted in defeat for the Elves, due to their lack of organization or technology. When such encounters did occur, the Elves usually tried to take advantage of the forests, where they would use bows with great accuracy to harass enemies from afar before retreating to safety. Because they are utterly non-aggressive and have little to trade, Elves have been left alone except when they occupy lands of forests to be used up, in which case the Elves have been driven away.
		
		As a race, the Elves believed in a fundamental balance and natural order to all living things. They saw themselves as the epitome of evolution, immortal and thus able to live forever but doing so in a society that puts no strain on the lands around them. With little else to occupy their time, they spent great efforts in nurturing their mental abilities. It should come as no surprise, then, that the Elves are true masters of magic that has been refined over thousands of years. 
		
		The Cataclysm was a time of great sorrow for the Elves. Following the Cataclysm, all of the  forests of the world died and no sapling grew for several years after. Although the Elves did not have much difficulty surviving without their source of food, spiritually the death of the forests was devastating to them. They had come to see the forests as their Mother, their Guardian. To see it killed off in an instant was a particularly traumatic experience.
		
		Thus, the Elves who survived the Cataclysm have decided to take a more direct approach in worldly matters. No longer content to leave their fate - or the fate of the forests - in the hands of the other races: the Elves now seek to control all magic in the world. Their ultimate goal is to prevent another Cataclysm and they believe that only through striving for the balance of magic they previously had can this goal be achieved. Elves are, because of this, particularly careful about sharing magical secrets with other races, whom they believe will not use it in a right way. Furthermore, the Elves have started to leave the forests to grow great cities out of stone and wood. While the forests are still worshiped as a deity - their Mother - they recognize that it is not in itself sentient and the Elves have therefore assumed the role of custodian for all the forests of the world. Though, the elven society is not without its own internal struggles. Building cities has created many new comforts for the Elves and while all recognize the necessity to reach for power in the world, some demand that the Elves return to their old ways rather than become weakened culturally by the new benefits of living in cities.</Description>
		<LorebookIntroText/>
		<AIPersonality>AI_General</AIPersonality>
		<Capital>Alfsigr</Capital>
		<City>Algar</City>
		<City>Alberich</City>
		<City>Alfhildr</City>
		<City>Alvar</City>
		<City>Alric</City>
		<City>Siofra</City>
		<City>Elfwood</City>
		<ShortName>Elves</ShortName>
		<PopulaceName>Elves</PopulaceName>
		<Alignment>Good</Alignment>
		<FactionAllegiance>Kingdom</FactionAllegiance>
		<SelAbilityBonusOption>NoDefensivestructures_Elf</SelAbilityBonusOption>
		<SelAbilityBonusOption>MasterworkChain</SelAbilityBonusOption>
		<SelAbilityBonusOption>Archers</SelAbilityBonusOption>
		<SelAbilityBonusOption>Rivermod_Golem2</SelAbilityBonusOption>
		<SelAbilityBonusOption>Ability_X_Deorcnysse1000</SelAbilityBonusOption>
		<MusicTheme>WanderersHome</MusicTheme>
		<DefaultCityWallSet>CPELF_CityWalls_Fence</DefaultCityWallSet>
		<NewCityHubType>CityHub1</NewCityHubType>
		<CapitalHubType>CityHub1</CapitalHubType>
		<RaceClassification>Elves</RaceClassification>
		<RaceDisplayName>Elves</RaceDisplayName>
		<RaceInternalName>Race_Type_Elves</RaceInternalName>
		<GenericUnitType_Male>Generic_Elves_Male</GenericUnitType_Male>
		<GenericUnitType_Female>Generic_Elves_Female</GenericUnitType_Female>
		<TraderUnitType>TraderTest</TraderUnitType>
		<ShopkeeperUnitType>Shopkeeper_Elves</ShopkeeperUnitType>
		<ChooseFactionBack>Faction_Background_Altar.png</ChooseFactionBack>
		<UnitScale>1</UnitScale>
		<UnitSkinColor>255,194,130</UnitSkinColor>
		<UnitHairColor>205,170,80</UnitHairColor>
		<UnitClothing1Color>62,91,60,255</UnitClothing1Color>
		<UnitClothing2Color>138,95,54,255</UnitClothing2Color>
		<UnitMetalColor>150,155,135,255</UnitMetalColor>
		<BuildingPrimaryColor>176,122,74</BuildingPrimaryColor>
		<BuildingSecondaryColor>79,48,20</BuildingSecondaryColor>
		<BuildingRoofColor>30,84,48</BuildingRoofColor>
		<ZoneOfControlColor>50,100,0</ZoneOfControlColor>
		<BuildingStyle>KingdomStyle</BuildingStyle>
		<TechTree>TechTree_X_Elves</TechTree>
		<EnvironmentTerrainType>2</EnvironmentTerrainType>
		<NonBuildableEnvironmentType>DeadEnvironment</NonBuildableEnvironmentType>
		<PreferredLogoType>elfcrest</PreferredLogoType>
		<SovereignUnitType>Sowien</SovereignUnitType>
	</RaceConfig>
	<RaceConfig InternalName="KingdomofLivingStone">
		<DisplayName>Living Stone #K</DisplayName>
		<Description>Slow and tough, the Living Stone are biological stones with fire in their veins.
		
		The Living Stone are the newest race to join the others in the Elemental world. They were created through some accident that took place at the Cataclysm, which they call the event of Creation. Far underground, perhaps by great pressure or some other unknown force, a Fire Shard exploded. This birthed the first of the Living Stone, quite literally stone men and women come alive. When they crawled to the surface of the world they were originally mistaken for Golems, and thus greatly feared. But the Living Stone, with no culture of their own, quickly adopted the Kingdom way of life, believing in the right to forge one's own destiny seeing as they had none of their own.
		
		Beyond that, very little is known about the Living Stone. Their bodies are on a biological level completely different from anything else in the world, so much that they cannot rightly be considered to be alive like others. Of course, noone who has ever met a living stone would make such a claim to their face. Their stony bodies allow them great power in battle, although they move much slower than a human would of the same size - no doubt their great weight is to blame. Amongst the Living Stone, only one moves and acts more "human" - their leader, Ceto. They say he was closest to the Fire Shard when it exploded, and empowered him, giving him his unique orange colour. Because he is more easily understood outside the Living Stone society, and also understands the surrounding world around them better, he now leads them. Unlike other sovereigns, Ceto was born with the ability to channel magic, rather than having to learn it, possibly a result of a shard quite literally being his creator.</Description>
		<LorebookIntroText>Slow and tough, the Living Stone are biological stones with fire in their veins.
		
		The Living Stone are the newest race to join the others in the Elemental world. They were created through some accident that took place at the Cataclysm, which they call the event of Creation. Far underground, perhaps by great pressure or some other unknown force, a Fire Shard exploded. This birthed the first of the Living Stone, quite literally stone men and women come alive. When they crawled to the surface of the world they were originally mistaken for Golems, and thus greatly feared. But the Living Stone, with no culture of their own, quickly adopted the Kingdom way of life, believing in the right to forge one's own destiny seeing as they had none of their own.
		
		Beyond that, very little is known about the Living Stone. Their bodies are on a biological level completely different from anything else in the world, so much that they cannot rightly be considered to be alive like others. Of course, noone who has ever met a living stone would make such a claim to their face. Their stony bodies allow them great power in battle, although they move much slower than a human would of the same size - no doubt their great weight is to blame. Amongst the Living Stone, only one moves and acts more "human" - their leader, Ceto. They say he was closest to the Fire Shard when it exploded, and empowered him, giving him his unique orange colour. Because he is more easily understood outside the Living Stone society, and also understands the surrounding world around them better, he now leads them. Unlike other sovereigns, Ceto was born with the ability to channel magic, rather than having to learn it, possibly a result of a shard quite literally being his creator.</LorebookIntroText>
		<AIPersonality>AI_General</AIPersonality>
		<Capital>Quathari</Capital>
		<City>Ngekil</City>
		<City>Biban</City>
		<City>Therset</City>
		<City>Okmo</City>
		<City>Thinere</City>
		<City>Daml</City>
		<City>Uspuz</City>
		<City>Fothi</City>
		<City>Thadi</City>
		<ShortName>Living Stone</ShortName>
		<LeaderName>Ceto, the Pillar</LeaderName>
		<PopulaceName>Living Stone</PopulaceName>
		<Alignment>Good</Alignment>
		<FactionAllegiance>Kingdom</FactionAllegiance>
		<SelAbilityBonusOption>LivingStone_Fireworship</SelAbilityBonusOption>
		<SelAbilityBonusOption>Rivermod_LivingStone</SelAbilityBonusOption>
		<SelAbilityBonusOption>Ability_X_Deorcnysse1000</SelAbilityBonusOption>
		<MusicTheme>WanderersHome</MusicTheme>
		<DefaultCityWallSet>CityWalls_Fence</DefaultCityWallSet>
		<NewCityHubType>CityHub1</NewCityHubType>
		<CapitalHubType>CityHub1</CapitalHubType>
		<RaceClassification>LivingStone</RaceClassification>
		<RaceDisplayName>Living Stone</RaceDisplayName>
		<RaceInternalName>Race_Type_LivingStone</RaceInternalName>
		<GenericUnitType_Male>Generic_LivingStone_Male</GenericUnitType_Male>
		<GenericUnitType_Female>Generic_LivingStone_Female</GenericUnitType_Female>
		<TraderUnitType>TraderTest</TraderUnitType>
		<ShopkeeperUnitType>Shopkeeper_LivingStone</ShopkeeperUnitType>
		<ChooseFactionBack>Faction_Background_Altar.png</ChooseFactionBack>
		<UnitScale>1</UnitScale>
		<UnitSkinColor>25,25,25</UnitSkinColor>
		<UnitHairColor>155,110,75</UnitHairColor>
		<UnitClothing1Color>120,25,20,255</UnitClothing1Color>
		<UnitClothing2Color>78,60,55,255</UnitClothing2Color>
		<UnitMetalColor>0,0,0,255</UnitMetalColor>
		<BuildingPrimaryColor>20,20,20</BuildingPrimaryColor>
		<BuildingSecondaryColor>20,20,20</BuildingSecondaryColor>
		<BuildingRoofColor>20,20,20</BuildingRoofColor>
		<ZoneOfControlColor>255,0,0</ZoneOfControlColor>
		<BuildingStyle>KingdomStyle</BuildingStyle>
		<TechTree>TechTree_X_LivingStone</TechTree>
		<EnvironmentTerrainType>2</EnvironmentTerrainType>
		<NonBuildableEnvironmentType>DeadEnvironment</NonBuildableEnvironmentType>
		<PreferredLogoType>livingstonecrest</PreferredLogoType>
		<SovereignUnitType>Sovereign_Ceto</SovereignUnitType>
	</RaceConfig>
	<RaceConfig InternalName="KingdomofShadows">
		<DisplayName>Shadows #K</DisplayName>
		<Description>Shadows are half-corporeal entities, able to alter their solid nature at a whim.
		
		A long time ago, before the Titans came to the Elemental world, there was an age of magic and wonder that no mortal will know again. During this age, many magical feats were accomplished that truly puts in perspective how futile the magic controlled today is.
		
		When magicians speak of those times, they speak of three events in particular that demonstrate the power then wielded that is now lost. The first of these was caused by Aman, who they said created the moon itself. The second of these is an object that was created that possessed infinite wonder and could not be described by any other words. The last of these, by Ul'rath, was the creation of the shadow people.
		
		Ul'rath was a young magician, and although powerful in his own rights, he was very much at a loss when he became smitten by a girl from the neighboring kingdom. Day and night he would court her, singing ballads, showing off magical feats, or in any way possible trying to get her attention. The girl was not easily swayed, and most agree she treated him unfairly by stringing him along for her amusement when she had no intention of marrying him.
		
		Although it was normal at the time that daughters were wed off, the kingdom the girl lived in had some laws that put all the power in the hands of the women. The laws said that any girl to be married had to question the manhood of any suitor and she would do so by proposing an act or a quest that the man had to accomplish. Of course, it doesn't take a genius to figure out that if the girl was interested in the man, the task was often as simple as throwing a rock or drinking a cup of ale. If the girl really did not like the man, an impossible task was set. 
		
		Eventually, Ul'rath had manipulated the girl's father into promising the girl to him, and thus the girl's only choice was to use the law to question his manhood and turn him away. Alas the girl was living in a world she did not understand. She asked for Ul'rath to give her his shadow as a token of his affection, to the mirth of all onlookers. The girl's father laughed but Ul'rath set his mind to the task and one week later arranged for the demonstration. At noon that day, Ul'rath poured all his magical power into achieving this goal and he succeeded in pulling his shadow from the ground.
		
		But the shadow was more than something Ul'rath could give away. It was a real, living entity, a corporeal two-dimensional being that had been forced into three dimensions by the magic of its maker. Thus, the Shadows were created.
		
		The story of Ul'rath ends there, although it is known that the girl eventually married him and that he lived all his days without his shadow.
		
		Many things are questioned when discussing the shadows. Are all shadows sentient? Or do they gain sentience when "created"? What is a shadow really, if it is not the darkness left behind by light that is stopped by something? How do the shadows multiply, as they have been doing since their creation?
		
		The shadows will speak only rarely and under duress as to the truth of such questions. They explain that they existed as two-dimensional beings, and that to explain what they remember before their making would be impossible. "Imagine", they say, "a world with no color, no light, no dark, no other combination of the spectrum. Then a man asks you to describe the color blue. That is what it means to understand the before and after of a Shadow." The first shadow made by Ul'rath, that calls itself Rud, was asked the same question and famously pointed to the sky and shouted: "Blue! Blue! Blue!". Thus, the Shadows are tolerated as they seem to not recall anything that happened to them before their making, their "making" being when they were torn from the two-dimensional existence into a corporeal form. As to how precisely they are made, that is mostly unknown, although Rud and many other shadows have become quite adept magicians themselves and ever since the Shadows first appeared as a race, the shadows of some people have gone missing, never to return.
		
		The Shadows themselves appear to have a physical form, and they can of course affect things around them like any normal man. But they are not always solid and a person can see through them most of the time. When attacked, they can grow less solid and thus avoid many wounds they would normally take. They wear special shadowforged armor that consists completely out of non-living shadows. This shadow armor mimics the real armor worn by other races. Strangely, shadows use "normal" weapons and shields, although exactly why that is has never been clarified.</Description>
		<LorebookIntroText/>
		<AIPersonality>AI_General</AIPersonality>
		<Capital>Biemas</Capital>
		<City>Chirani</City>
		<City>Ceawyth</City>
		<City>Shadowkeep</City>
		<City>Nightfall</City>
		<City>Sunset</City>
		<City>Crandra</City>
		<City>Meliron</City>
		<City>Sevoth</City>
		<City>Roikith</City>
		<ShortName>Shadows</ShortName>
		<LeaderName>Edror</LeaderName>
		<PopulaceName>Shadows</PopulaceName>
		<Alignment>Good</Alignment>
		<FactionAllegiance>Kingdom</FactionAllegiance>
		<SelAbilityBonusOption>ShadowLimit</SelAbilityBonusOption>
		<SelAbilityBonusOption>Shadowarmor</SelAbilityBonusOption>
		<SelAbilityBonusOption>NoRangedWeapons</SelAbilityBonusOption>
		<SelAbilityBonusOption>Rivermod_blockmagmaforge</SelAbilityBonusOption>
		<SelAbilityBonusOption>Ability_X_Deorcnysse1000</SelAbilityBonusOption>
		<MusicTheme>WanderersHome</MusicTheme>
		<DefaultCityWallSet>CityWalls_Fence</DefaultCityWallSet>
		<NewCityHubType>CityHub1</NewCityHubType>
		<CapitalHubType>CityHub1</CapitalHubType>
		<RaceClassification>Shadows</RaceClassification>
		<RaceDisplayName>Shadows</RaceDisplayName>
		<RaceInternalName>Race_Type_Shadows</RaceInternalName>
		<GenericUnitType_Male>Generic_Shadows_Male</GenericUnitType_Male>
		<GenericUnitType_Female>Generic_Shadows_Female</GenericUnitType_Female>
		<TraderUnitType>TraderTest</TraderUnitType>
		<ShopkeeperUnitType>Shopkeeper_Shadows</ShopkeeperUnitType>
		<ChooseFactionBack>Faction_Background_Altar.png</ChooseFactionBack>
		<UnitScale>1</UnitScale>
		<UnitSkinColor>215,150,100</UnitSkinColor>
		<UnitHairColor>155,110,75</UnitHairColor>
		<UnitClothing1Color>220,220,220,255</UnitClothing1Color>
		<UnitClothing2Color>100,100,100</UnitClothing2Color>
		<UnitMetalColor>255,255,255</UnitMetalColor>
		<BuildingPrimaryColor>200,200,200</BuildingPrimaryColor>
		<BuildingSecondaryColor>79,48,20</BuildingSecondaryColor>
		<BuildingRoofColor>30,84,48</BuildingRoofColor>
		<ZoneOfControlColor>140,77,166</ZoneOfControlColor>
		<BuildingStyle>KingdomStyle</BuildingStyle>
		<TechTree>TechTree_X_Shadows</TechTree>
		<EnvironmentTerrainType>2</EnvironmentTerrainType>
		<NonBuildableEnvironmentType>DeadEnvironment</NonBuildableEnvironmentType>
		<PreferredLogoType>shadowcrest</PreferredLogoType>
		<SovereignUnitType>Edror_398510779-546</SovereignUnitType>
	</RaceConfig>
	<RaceConfig InternalName="EmpireofDeathLegion">
		<DisplayName>Chaos Legion #E</DisplayName>
		<Description>The Chaos Legion is a race of demons. They used to inhabit one of the planes of the Dungeon Dimensions but were banished following events leading up to the Cataclysm. Their physical forms are constantly changing, by the harnessed corruption of their home realm bound in their bodies. 
		
		The Dungeon Dimensions are completely alien to how we think of as the Elemental world. It is most easily described by likening it to some sort of hell where many different demon races fight each other back and forth for dominion. Each area is different from the next: one may be a seemingly endless land of black sand where you can see some manner of night sky, another a cave system that leads into larger caves. They all share some traits, however. Without fail, each and every one is more like a battlefield than anything else. The Dungeon Dimensions are also profoundly magical and most believe that this is the reason why there is constantly so much violence in them. New powers are endlessly emerging or evolving and older powers seek to control them or avoid being destroyed by them. In some areas, demons are bred like cattle to fight and die in the wars of the demonlords. Thus the Dungeon Dimensions exist in a state of war that drags on forever, only halted by the occasional failed attack or defeat of a race.
		
		The Chaos Legion is the losing side of such a struggle. Emerging as a fighting power around five thousand years ago, they struggled with local powers until they had achieved a patch of land to call their own. Their power was drawn from red powerstones found in the quarries beneath their lands. It turned them into great fighters, highly violent, but also gave them an unquenchable temper and made them prone to rash actions without considering the long-term goals of the race.
		
		Thus, they assumed a position of offense by attacking and butchering the other demon races in nearby lands, until they met their match around 50 years before the Cataclysm. In that time, they initiated what began as a successful siege of a vast fortress controlled by a bordering demonlord. However, the brute force and overwhelming numbers of the Chaos Legion were beaten aside by the massively intelligent demonlord who was defending the fortress. Older than the Chaos Legion itself, the demonlord drew from his experiences of thousands of years on the battlefield and arranged for supply lines to be interrupted and frequent flanking attacks to upset the camps of the Chaos Legion. The strategy proved effective and, faced with an indestructible fortress ahead to halt their violence and being outmaneuvered by flankers in the areas around the fortress, the Chaos Legion found itself in a dangerous situation. After fifty years of sieging the fortress, the Chaos Legion had become more entrenched and dependent on their own defenses to survive, than the fortress they had attempted to destroy. When the defenders of the fortress began a series of attempts to break out, the Chaos Legion lost all faith that they would succeed and decided to break camp.
		
		Thus it was that, at the time of the Cataclysm, the Chaos Legion was in full retreat and being hounded by enemies on all sides swooping in to take advantage of the Chaos Legion's changing fortune. Taking advantage of the needlessly spent resources of the Chaos Legion, their enemies did not stop pursuing them and soon the lands were taken over by various factions. What forces remained began a long walk away from whatever hostile force was most threatening every day but being surrounded by enemies, such a strategy could not succeed.
		
		The exodus came to an end when they reached the gates leading into another dimension. Now facing certain extinction and with no end of enemies in sight, the Chaos Legion hoped to leave the area and restart elsewhere by traveling through the dimension gates. There, all those races who wanted them gone had gathered a great army to defeat them. The leader of the Chaos Legion, dubbed the No-god, used all of his magic to open up the gates, while the magic of the enemies was directed to try to keep them closed. During the final struggle, the external event called the Cataclysm occurred and, perhaps drawn to the powers channeled into the gates, scattered the remains of the Chaos Legion across all of the Dungeon Dimensions. But not all were lost though: a few thousand appeared in the Elemental world.
		
		The Chaos Legion were cut off from an existence they understood and more importantly their leader. At first they thought this new land was soft and easily conquered but quickly changed their minds as their scarcity in numbers, leadership, and supply of red powerstones made them an easy target by raiders. Where they used to depend on brute force and having a great number of soldiers that were expendable, their tactics initially proved ruinous. At the same time, many of the other races banded together against them to rid the world of a demon invasion.
		
		The Chaos Legion now faces a precarious situation where they must attempt diplomacy, unthinkable in the Dungeon Dimensions where none can be trusted, for them to have a chance at growing in strength again. Fortunately, they lack this thing called "morality" that many other races seem to think is of such great importance. It will be a cold day in Hell before a demon is beaten in a fair fight by a mere man.</Description>
		<LorebookIntroText/>
		<AIPersonality>AI_General</AIPersonality>
		<Capital>Kizabikar</Capital>
		<City>Dunospfitha</City>
		<City>Gamorulku</City>
		<City>Bukzakareb</City>
		<City>Itijamol</City>
		<City>Ecems</City>
		<City>Piklil</City>
		<City>Rsenotsta</City>
		<City>Oprigfera</City>
		<City>Gethor</City>
		<ShortName>Chaos Legion</ShortName>
		<LeaderName>Irathiiv</LeaderName>
		<PopulaceName>Chaos Legion</PopulaceName>
		<Alignment>Evil</Alignment>
		<FactionAllegiance>Empire</FactionAllegiance>
		<SelAbilityBonusOption>DeathLegionLimit</SelAbilityBonusOption>
		<SelAbilityBonusOption>FleshBoundTome</SelAbilityBonusOption>
		<SelAbilityBonusOption>Rivermod_DeathLegion</SelAbilityBonusOption>
		<SelAbilityBonusOption>Rivermod_NoBloodForge</SelAbilityBonusOption>
		<SelAbilityBonusOption>Ability_X_Deorcnysse1000</SelAbilityBonusOption>
		<MusicTheme>WanderersHome</MusicTheme>
		<DefaultCityWallSet>CityWalls_Fence</DefaultCityWallSet>
		<NewCityHubType>CityHub1</NewCityHubType>
		<CapitalHubType>CityHub1</CapitalHubType>
		<RaceClassification>DeathLegion</RaceClassification>
		<RaceDisplayName>Chaos Legion</RaceDisplayName>
		<RaceInternalName>Race_Type_DeathLegion</RaceInternalName>
		<GenericUnitType_Male>Generic_DeathLegion_Male</GenericUnitType_Male>
		<GenericUnitType_Female>Generic_DeathLegion_Female</GenericUnitType_Female>
		<TraderUnitType>TraderTest</TraderUnitType> 
		<ShopkeeperUnitType>Shopkeeper_DeathLegion</ShopkeeperUnitType>
		<ChooseFactionBack>Faction_Background_Altar.png</ChooseFactionBack>
		<UnitScale>1</UnitScale>
		<UnitSkinColor>20,0,0</UnitSkinColor>
		<UnitHairColor>155,110,75</UnitHairColor>
		<UnitClothing1Color>120,25,20,255</UnitClothing1Color>
		<UnitClothing2Color>78,60,55,255</UnitClothing2Color>
		<UnitMetalColor>0,0,0,255</UnitMetalColor>
		<BuildingPrimaryColor>0,0,0</BuildingPrimaryColor>
		<BuildingSecondaryColor>35,0,0</BuildingSecondaryColor>
		<BuildingRoofColor>100,100,100</BuildingRoofColor>
		<ZoneOfControlColor>98,0,0</ZoneOfControlColor>
		<BuildingStyle>EmpireStyle</BuildingStyle>
		<TechTree>TechTree_X_ChaosLegion</TechTree>
		<EnvironmentTerrainType>1</EnvironmentTerrainType>
		<NonBuildableEnvironmentType>GrasslandEnvironment</NonBuildableEnvironmentType>
		<PreferredLogoType>KingdomCrest6</PreferredLogoType>
		<SovereignUnitType>Irathiiv_903400073-427</SovereignUnitType>
	</RaceConfig>
	<RaceConfig InternalName="EmpireOfDrota">
		<DisplayName>Drota #E</DisplayName>
		<Description>The Drota became Spider hybrids during the Cataclysm, and are well-known for their desire to hunt all living things.
		
		The Drota is one of the most ancient races - older than even mankind - that is native to the Elemental world. They hunted dragons more than five thousand years ago, and have undergone many shifts in culture. They put a lot of effort into recording and maintaining their history, in particular their successful hunters and their bloodlines.
		
		However, the one thousand years before the Cataclysm mostly saw the Drota killed off due to their tribal structure and insistence on "hunting" all the other races of the world. The Drota are at heart hunters and by far the best hunters in the world. This was deeply ingrained in their hierarchies, with the best hunter also leading the tribe. A tribal leader that did not lead the tribe on constant hunts was thrown out. Because of this reason, diplomatic relations with the Drota have always failed within a few years. Indeed, it is difficult to negotiate deals with an entity that almost constantly smiles at you and tells you how he's going to "hunt you down". The century before the Cataclysm, the Drota were almost completely conquered by the other races and was more considered a pest, performing the occasional raid on the countryside rather than any true danger to civilization. This was also enforced due to their inability to use the magic in the shards. The coming of the Titans and their gathering of all magic into the shards meant that the Drota's ancient magic was turned powerless over the course of a few weeks.
		
		70 years before the Cataclysm, a new leader emerged, dubbed the Stormlord by the Drota. She was the first Drota to manage channeling from the Shards. The Drota tell of how the Stormlord made a deal with some extraterrestrial being, where she traded her "little brother" (an organ that grants the Drota great regenerative abilities) for the ability to channel magic again. The Stormlord then used her power to lead her spider cult to dominion over all the Drota tribes. This ensured the Drota were once again a threat to all other races just before the Cataclysm. 
		
		But not even the Drota could imagine what would happen during the Cataclysm. Even to this day there are many who will tell the story differently. What is known with certainty is this: before the Cataclysm, the Drota were humanoids like any other, with two legs, arms, and a head. After the Cataclysm, the Stormlord and her closest followers had turned into a hybrid between spider and Drota. The upper body remained intact, but the lower body had been replaced by the body of a spider, only with six legs instead of eight.
		
		Some say the Stormlord was granted this great boon for her loyal worshiping of some obscure spider god. Others say the Cataclysm merely happened while the Stormlord was in the act of performing some unholy union between spider and Drota and the great surge in magic caused the hybrids to form.
		
		The century after the Cataclysm saw a civil war amongst the Drota, where the spider cult eventually enslaved all other Drota and forced them to bear hybrid children. Their new hybrid bodies granted them greatly enhanced abilities that assisted them in the various hunts performed. The Drota are now a very different species compared to that which existed before the Cataclysm. Their military power is mostly untested against other races but it seems clear from early contact with the Drota that their cultural preference for war and "hunting" remains. 
		</Description>
		<LorebookIntroText/>
		<AIPersonality>AI_General</AIPersonality>
		<Capital>Quathari</Capital>
		<City>Ashsh</City>
		<City>Laerd</City>
		<City>Adch</City>
		<City>Etani</City>
		<City>Whaych</City>
		<City>Eyre</City>
		<City>Keild</City>
		<City>Nult</City>
		<City>Imr</City>
		<ShortName>Drotas</ShortName>
		<LeaderName>Stormlord</LeaderName>
		<PopulaceName>Constructs</PopulaceName>
		<Alignment>Evil</Alignment>
		<FactionAllegiance>Empire</FactionAllegiance>
		<SelAbilityBonusOption>MasterworkChain</SelAbilityBonusOption>
		<SelAbilityBonusOption>Rivermod_Drota</SelAbilityBonusOption>
		<SelAbilityBonusOption>MasterScout_Drota</SelAbilityBonusOption>
		<SelAbilityBonusOption>CultofaHundredEyes</SelAbilityBonusOption>
		<SelAbilityBonusOption>Weakness_X_Gourmets</SelAbilityBonusOption>
		<SelAbilityBonusOption>Weakness_X_Slaughterers</SelAbilityBonusOption>
		<SelAbilityBonusOption>Ability_X_Deorcnysse1000</SelAbilityBonusOption>
		<MusicTheme>WanderersHome</MusicTheme>
		<DefaultCityWallSet>CityWalls_Fence</DefaultCityWallSet>
		<NewCityHubType>CityHub1</NewCityHubType>
		<CapitalHubType>CityHub1</CapitalHubType>
		<RaceClassification>Drota</RaceClassification>
		<RaceDisplayName>Drota</RaceDisplayName>
		<RaceInternalName>Race_Type_Drota</RaceInternalName>
		<GenericUnitType_Male>Generic_Drota_Male</GenericUnitType_Male>
		<GenericUnitType_Female>Generic_Drota_Female</GenericUnitType_Female>
		<TraderUnitType>TraderTest</TraderUnitType>
		<ShopkeeperUnitType>Shopkeeper_Drota</ShopkeeperUnitType>
		<ChooseFactionBack>Faction_Background_Altar.png</ChooseFactionBack>
		<UnitScale>1</UnitScale>
		<UnitSkinColor>66,66,66</UnitSkinColor>
		<UnitHairColor>155,110,75</UnitHairColor>
		<UnitClothing1Color>120,25,20,255</UnitClothing1Color>
		<UnitClothing2Color>78,60,55,255</UnitClothing2Color>
		<UnitMetalColor>255,255,255</UnitMetalColor>
		<BuildingPrimaryColor>100,100,100</BuildingPrimaryColor>
		<BuildingSecondaryColor>100,100,100</BuildingSecondaryColor>
		<BuildingRoofColor>100,100,100</BuildingRoofColor>
		<ZoneOfControlColor>200,70,0</ZoneOfControlColor>
		<BuildingStyle>EmpireStyle</BuildingStyle>
		<TechTree>TechTree_X_Drota</TechTree>
		<EnvironmentTerrainType>1</EnvironmentTerrainType>
		<NonBuildableEnvironmentType>GrasslandEnvironment</NonBuildableEnvironmentType>
		<PreferredLogoType>GenericCrest40</PreferredLogoType>
		<SovereignUnitType>Mublada_-762136301-492</SovereignUnitType>
	</RaceConfig>
	<RaceConfig InternalName="EmpireofFrostGiants">
		<DisplayName>Frost Giants #E</DisplayName>
		<Description>From a land of cold and darkness come the Frost Giants. Huge beings of immense powers, they represent military might the like of which has never been seen on Elemental before.
		
		The Frost Giants have always been a nagging presence in the world of Elemental. Before the Cataclysm, they inhabited a great continent north of the world that was permanently covered in ice. Perhaps this is why you'll rarely find a hint of their existence in the history books made by the Human races. The Frost Giants kept to themselves and were content to stay inside the environment they preferred. Concurrently, they had nothing to offer in trade or resources and thus were left alone by the free merchants. 
		
		Forced to conserve energy, Frost Giants regularly went into hibernation during the coldest months of the years but it was not uncommon for this hibernation to last several years for some. This and the fact that the Frost Giants lacked any real hierarchy meant that other diplomatic relations were difficult to maintain and eventually all contact broke down, condemned as pointless. 
		
		The Frost Giants possess an unnatural ability to somehow draw energy from being cold. This is what allowed them to survive in a land covered in snow all year around. They lived in small tribes with few connections to others, except young males that would always leave their tribe and join another when entering adulthood. They possessed little in terms of culture and they had only a few tools made out of stones and twinned hair.
		
		During the Cataclysm, the entire continent of the Frost Giants sank beneath the oceans. A few Frost Giants were able to survive by climbing aboard icebergs that they then willed south by magic. 
		
		The Frost Giants arrived at the beaches of the Elemental continent and quickly established themselves as a power to be reckoned with. Although not clear from before the Cataclysm, the Frost Giants live exceptionally long lives, and only continue to grow as they do so. Thus, a Frost Giant army can vary greatly in power, regardless of how many they actually bring to the fight. The youngest are not much taller than any men, while the oldest can stand thrice as tall as the tallest man. Their giant physique makes fighting them very difficult, as they are so unlike any other race in size and power. 
		
		The Cataclysm has been a significant event in Frost Giant history. They had little culture before the Cataclysm but they did love their land and now blame the other races in the world for causing the utter annihilation of their continent. The Frost Giants primarily seek vengeance on all of the magicians in the Elemental world, whom they blame for the Cataclysm, even if none were alive back then (it is, as they call it, the "inherited sin" of the "worldbreakers"). The Frost Giants also seek to turn this continent into a new homeland by covering all the world in eternal snow. 
		
		Another recent change in Frost Giant society is the elevation of their channelers. Before those were scorned for their lack of physical prowess but not even the dumbest Frost Giant can deny that it was only thanks to their channelers, who steered the icebergs south when their continent sank, that the Frost Giants are even alive today. Others are also beginning to take notice of the massive difference in mental capacity between a normal Frost Giant and a channeler. Hence, the channelers have been given an honorary status at the very top of the hierarchy, above the oldest of warriors.</Description>
		<LorebookIntroText/>
		<AIPersonality>AI_General</AIPersonality>
		<Capital>Jotunheim</Capital>
		<City>Hel</City>
		<City>Reynes</City>
		<City>Agartha</City>
		<City>Lemuria</City>
		<City>Nyrsa</City>
		<City>Thule</City>
		<City>Ys</City>
		<City>Kvenland</City>
		<ShortName>Frost Giants</ShortName>
		<LeaderName>Hofund</LeaderName>
		<PopulaceName>Frost Giants</PopulaceName>
		<Alignment>Evil</Alignment>
		<FactionAllegiance>Empire</FactionAllegiance>
		<SelAbilityBonusOption>Player_X_FrostGiants_Bases</SelAbilityBonusOption>
		<SelAbilityBonusOption>FrostGiant_Frostfire</SelAbilityBonusOption>
		<SelAbilityBonusOption>Rivermod_blockmagmaforge</SelAbilityBonusOption>
		<SelAbilityBonusOption>Ability_X_Deorcnysse1000</SelAbilityBonusOption>
		<MusicTheme>WanderersHome</MusicTheme>
		<DefaultCityWallSet>CityWalls_Fence</DefaultCityWallSet>
		<NewCityHubType>CityHub1</NewCityHubType>
		<CapitalHubType>CityHub1</CapitalHubType>
		<RaceClassification>FrostGiants</RaceClassification>
		<RaceDisplayName>Frost Giants</RaceDisplayName>
		<RaceInternalName>Race_Type_FrostGiants</RaceInternalName>
		<GenericUnitType_Male>Generic_FrostGiants_Male</GenericUnitType_Male>
		<GenericUnitType_Female>Generic_FrostGiants_Female</GenericUnitType_Female>
		<TraderUnitType>TraderTest</TraderUnitType>
		<ShopkeeperUnitType>Shopkeeper_FrostGiants</ShopkeeperUnitType>
		<ChooseFactionBack>Faction_Background_Altar.png</ChooseFactionBack>
		<UnitScale>1</UnitScale>
		<UnitSkinColor>255,255,255</UnitSkinColor>
		<UnitHairColor>255,255,255</UnitHairColor>
		<UnitClothing1Color>130,165,190</UnitClothing1Color>
		<UnitClothing2Color>130,165,190</UnitClothing2Color>
		<UnitMetalColor>130,165,190</UnitMetalColor>
		<BuildingPrimaryColor>165,145,130</BuildingPrimaryColor>
		<BuildingSecondaryColor>75,60,50</BuildingSecondaryColor>
		<BuildingRoofColor>90,15,10</BuildingRoofColor>
		<ZoneOfControlColor>50,50,250</ZoneOfControlColor>
		<BuildingStyle>EmpireStyle</BuildingStyle>
		<TechTree>TechTree_X_FrostGiants</TechTree>
		<EnvironmentTerrainType>1</EnvironmentTerrainType>
		<NonBuildableEnvironmentType>GrasslandEnvironment</NonBuildableEnvironmentType>
		<PreferredLogoType>frostgiantlogo</PreferredLogoType>
		<SovereignUnitType>SovereignFrostGiants</SovereignUnitType>
	</RaceConfig>
	<RaceConfig InternalName="EmpireofGolem">
		<DisplayName>Golems #E</DisplayName>
		<Description>The Golem faction consists primarily of White Golems made by the White Wizard many thousand years ago. They are partially made out of souls of sacrificed humans. They also have a small amount of dust in them taken from the magical shards, and have shown great resistance to magic.
		
		Throughout the years, there have been many magicians and wizards who made for themselves golems to serve. But none created more than the The White Wizard, who lived before the Titans came. To him, they replaced servants, family and friends. But because they did so, he lived his life as a boy, his golems shouldering all duty. As he passed on, he had not a thought for the fate of his creations. Left without a master, no more golems were made and they had no purpose. Performing their tasks, they spread across the world and did strange things, trying to find meaning in every word their creator had said, looking for meaning in implications, subtexts, and chiffers. But there was none to be had. The White Wizard lived the life of a genius, but he died as young in his mind as he ever was. 
		
		After many years, when the golems had grown few, and had changed in many ways, another man took pity on these machinations walking in his lands. His name was Diego, and he cared for these golems that wandered the land but didn't think for themselves. And though he laboured all his life to repair golems he found, and attempted to create ways for them to reproduce, his life was by any human standards wasted. But the golems had watched him labour, as much as Diego had watched them. And by discussing and analyzing the life of Diego, whom the golems had thought of as friend, they at last found the solution to their problems. They saw in Diego what no golem had ever understood - that to live is to love, and want, and sacrifice, and make your own fate. Not to mindlessly serve based on instructions from others. So the golems set about to find their own fate. And the first of these were Lochean, who gathered all the golems together, and through channeling again could create more. 
		
		The history of the golems is commonly depicted in their cities in various ornaments. There, the White Wizard sits on a rug, held aloft by perfectly identical golems - they call him Maker. And there Diego lies dead on the ground, tools scattered around him, with the many different golems watching him - they call him Father. And at last, Lochean, with both arms raised to the skies, as if to challenge the future, with golems lined up behind him nearing infinity - they call him Brother.
		
		The golems that followed Lochean into true sentience all share a common characteristic - in their presence, magic is very weak. It is believed that this occurs due to how the golems were - and are - made, with some magical dust sprinkled into the golem at creation. Some say the dust is made out of broken shards, although that is unlikely since the shards didn't exist on Elemental when the White Wizard lived.</Description>
		<LorebookIntroText/>
		<AIPersonality>AI_General</AIPersonality>
		<Capital>First</Capital>
		<City>Second</City>
		<City>Third</City>
		<City>Fourth</City>
		<City>Fifth</City>
		<City>Sixth</City>
		<City>Seventh</City>
		<City>Ninth</City>
		<City>Tenth</City>
		<City>Eleventh</City>
		<ShortName>Golems</ShortName>
		<LeaderName>Lochean</LeaderName>
		<PopulaceName>Constructs</PopulaceName>
		<Alignment>Evil</Alignment>
		<FactionAllegiance>Empire</FactionAllegiance>
		<SelAbilityBonusOption>Player_X_Golems</SelAbilityBonusOption>
		<SelAbilityBonusOption>Rivermod_Golem</SelAbilityBonusOption>
		<SelAbilityBonusOption>Rivermod_Golem2</SelAbilityBonusOption>
		<SelAbilityBonusOption>Ability_X_Deorcnysse1000</SelAbilityBonusOption>
		<MusicTheme>WanderersHome</MusicTheme>
		<DefaultCityWallSet>CityWalls_Fence</DefaultCityWallSet>
		<NewCityHubType>CityHub1</NewCityHubType>
		<CapitalHubType>CityHub1</CapitalHubType>
		<RaceClassification>Golem</RaceClassification>
		<RaceDisplayName>Golem</RaceDisplayName>
		<RaceInternalName>Race_Type_Golem</RaceInternalName>
		<GenericUnitType_Male>Generic_Golem_Male</GenericUnitType_Male>
		<GenericUnitType_Female>Generic_Golem_Female</GenericUnitType_Female>
		<TraderUnitType>TraderTest</TraderUnitType>
		<ShopkeeperUnitType>Shopkeeper_Golem</ShopkeeperUnitType>
		<ChooseFactionBack>Faction_Background_Altar.png</ChooseFactionBack>
		<UnitScale>1</UnitScale>
		<UnitSkinColor>255,255,255</UnitSkinColor>
		<UnitHairColor>155,110,75</UnitHairColor>
		<UnitClothing1Color>120,25,20,255</UnitClothing1Color>
		<UnitClothing2Color>78,60,55,255</UnitClothing2Color>
		<UnitMetalColor>255,255,255</UnitMetalColor>
		<BuildingPrimaryColor>255,255,255</BuildingPrimaryColor>
		<BuildingSecondaryColor>255,255,255</BuildingSecondaryColor>
		<BuildingRoofColor>255,255,255</BuildingRoofColor>
		<ZoneOfControlColor>100,115,174</ZoneOfControlColor>
		<BuildingStyle>EmpireStyle</BuildingStyle>
		<TechTree>TechTree_X_Golems</TechTree>
		<EnvironmentTerrainType>1</EnvironmentTerrainType>
		<NonBuildableEnvironmentType>GrasslandEnvironment</NonBuildableEnvironmentType>
		<PreferredLogoType>GenericCrest32</PreferredLogoType>
		<SovereignUnitType>Lochean_1585768275-495</SovereignUnitType>
	</RaceConfig>
	<RaceConfig InternalName="EmpireOfLizardmen">
		<DisplayName>Lizardmen #E</DisplayName>
		<Description>Ancient reptiles practicing blood magic.
		
		The Lizardmen were the first civilization to rise on Elemental, some 30 000 years before the Cataclysm. Being the only civilized beings in the world at the time, they effectively ruled the entire world. They erected vast temples where they sacrificed their own kind to appease the "Great Eye," the Sun god. The society was ruled by a class of priests that were also considered royalty because of their divine blood.
		
		The study of blood magic led the Lizardmen down a dark path. With the discovery of the Blood Curse, they found that they could sacrifice almost everybody of their race in order to make the priests into demi-gods. The priests were unable to restrain themselves in their religious fervor and the Lizardmen civilization was decimated as everyone was systematically sacrificed in a gigantic genocide. The priests, having achieved their long-sought dreams of becoming closer to the gods, went mad with hubris. They tried to war against the six Primordial Elements and were utterly destroyed. Thousands of years later the Elves would find the ruins of their mighty civilization and wonder at what came before.
		
		However, the Lizardmen did not all die. A few of the priests' children, gifted with extraordinarily long lives by the Blood Curse spell, hid in the depths of the world as the Primordial Elements destroyed their parents. Only rarely did they venture out; thus the Lizardmen existed on the brink of annihilation for almost thirty thousand years - at no point did they number more than a few hundred. Their society - or what was left of it - was stagnant. For the survivors, this was punishment from the gods for their mad priests' actions.
		
		They did not, however, abandon their old practices. Hidden in the depths, they waited for the time to return to rule the world; for it must surely be so, according to their religion. Time is circular to them and all that passes will return one day. A power that rises will fall and rise in turn, forever. As such, the Cataclysm was a catalyst to the Lizardmen. Their waking call.</Description>
		<LorebookIntroText/>
		<AIPersonality>AI_General</AIPersonality>
		<Capital>Uxmal</Capital>
		<City>Lustria</City>
		<City>Sayil</City>
		<City>Palenqua</City>
		<City>Caracol</City>
		<City>Yacetec</City>
		<City>Tikal</City>
		<City>Copan</City>
		<City>Tulum</City>
		<City>Cuelle</City>
		<ShortName>Lizardmen</ShortName>
		<LeaderName>Omiss</LeaderName>
		<PopulaceName>Lizardmen</PopulaceName>
		<Alignment>Evil</Alignment>
		<FactionAllegiance>Empire</FactionAllegiance>
		<SelAbilityBonusOption>Player_X_Lizardmen</SelAbilityBonusOption>
		<SelAbilityBonusOption>Rivermod_Lizardmen</SelAbilityBonusOption>
		<SelAbilityBonusOption>Weakness_X_Ascetics</SelAbilityBonusOption>
		<SelAbilityBonusOption>Ability_X_Deorcnysse1000</SelAbilityBonusOption>
		<MusicTheme>WanderersHome</MusicTheme>
		<DefaultCityWallSet>CityWalls_Fence</DefaultCityWallSet>
		<NewCityHubType>CityHub1</NewCityHubType>
		<CapitalHubType>CityHub1</CapitalHubType>
		<RaceClassification>Lizardmen</RaceClassification>
		<RaceDisplayName>Lizardmen</RaceDisplayName>
		<RaceInternalName>Race_Type_Lizardmen</RaceInternalName>
		<GenericUnitType_Male>Generic_Lizardmen_Male</GenericUnitType_Male>
		<GenericUnitType_Female>Generic_Lizardmen_Female</GenericUnitType_Female>
		<TraderUnitType>TraderTest</TraderUnitType>
		<ShopkeeperUnitType>Shopkeeper_Lizardmen</ShopkeeperUnitType>
		<ChooseFactionBack>Faction_Background_Altar.png</ChooseFactionBack>
		<UnitScale>1</UnitScale>
		<UnitSkinColor>77,77,0</UnitSkinColor>
		<UnitHairColor>28,21,0</UnitHairColor>
		<UnitClothing1Color>99,63,30</UnitClothing1Color>
		<UnitClothing2Color>78,65,50</UnitClothing2Color>
		<UnitMetalColor>70,70,16</UnitMetalColor>
		<BuildingPrimaryColor>56,33,13</BuildingPrimaryColor>
		<BuildingSecondaryColor>77,77,0</BuildingSecondaryColor>
		<BuildingRoofColor>77,77,0</BuildingRoofColor>
		<ZoneOfControlColor>70,70,16</ZoneOfControlColor>
		<BuildingStyle>EmpireStyle</BuildingStyle>
		<TechTree>TechTree_X_Lizardmen</TechTree>
		<EnvironmentTerrainType>1</EnvironmentTerrainType>
		<NonBuildableEnvironmentType>DeadEnvironment</NonBuildableEnvironmentType>
		<PreferredLogoType>logo_lizardmen</PreferredLogoType>
		<SovereignUnitType>Sovereign_X_Omiss</SovereignUnitType>
	</RaceConfig>
	<RaceConfig InternalName="EmpireofUndead">
		<DisplayName>Undead #E</DisplayName>
		<Description>From a long-dead kingdom arose the Undead - living skeletons bound together by dark magic.
		
		The Undead as most think of them today - a coherent faction instead of the occasional zombie crawling out of a grave - rose out of an old human kingdom. In this kingdom, the Fifth Patriarch who was the ruler of all the land, had become obsessed with the matter of life and death. His interest in the matter only increased as he - first of an unbroken line of over twenty rulers - had not sired any sons or daughters to take his place when he would pass on.
		
		The Fifth Patriarch then gathered all the nobles and monks and generals and learned civilians to his castle, where he set them to various tasks to test their characters. Quickly, he was able to eliminate from the candidates those who were only seeking power or personal gain. However his kingdom was vast and there were many philosophies represented amongst the remaining contenders, and the Fifth Patriarch's days were growing fewer and fewer.
		
		The Fifth Patriarch then asked that those who remained would attempt to express their wisdom in a poem. The focus would be on life and death and the original nature of mankind. This was meant to ultimately reveal the true heart of those who remained. 
		
		For one day and one night, the contenders wrote their poems. And at daybreak, they all read them for the Fifth Patriarch and his advisers. While the advisers all favored one poem from a boy that claimed that the soul was profoundly nothingness and so could never be filled with darkness, the Fifth Patriarch was of a different opinion. He focused instead on another poem, that likened the soul to a mirror that reflected all things, which one must keep clean or have it become dusty and unreadable.
		
		Because the Fifth Patriarch had his obsession of life and death (and even feared death in private) the ability to wipe away all the stains on one's soul greatly appealed to him. The Fifth Patriarch then called all his greatest magicians and wizards to his side, and ordered them to attempt to 'clean his mirror', no matter the cost. And for seven days and seven nights they unleashed great magic tailored for the task and when one week had passed, the Fifth Patriarch had died from exhaustion. 
		
		Those responsible for the spells feared retribution from the contenders for having killed the Fifth Patriarch, who was loved throughout the kingdom. They therefore summoned the only remaining order of magicians that had not been called to the task of scrubbing the Fifth Patriarch's soul, 'the Necromancers'. The Necromancers were at best tolerated within the kingdom, for they dabbled in dark magic that was said to be able to return the dead to life. Their practice was effectively banned because it required human sacrifice. Now called to the dead Patriarch's side, five of the magicians offered their lives to the Necromancers if the Fifth Patriarch could be returned to life. After all, the Fifth Patriarch had yet to rule who of the contenders would succeed him, so the five magicians considered this a small price to pay to save the kingdom.
		
		What exactly happened next is a matter of debate. Some say the Necromancers betrayed their task and created the Skeleton King out of the remains of the Fifth Patriarch. Others say that the magicians had effectively destroyed the soul of the Fifth Patriarch, and so when the Necromancers attempted to recall his soul to his body, they got something else instead. Regardless, it is known that when the night had passed, the Skeleton King had been created. His flesh burned away by the spells, dark magic now kept his bones together and moving.
		
		Following this ordeal, the born Skeleton King coerced the Necromancers into teaching him their knowledge. And within months the entire ruling caste had been turned into the Undead skeletons, now ruled by the evil Skeleton King.</Description>
		<LorebookIntroText/>
		<AIPersonality>AI_General</AIPersonality>
		<Capital>Golgotterath</Capital>
		<City>Rhoacien</City>
		<City>Erauwa</City>
		<City>Eil-anad</City>
		<City>Eajir</City>
		<City>Gravehold</City>
		<City>Deathkeep</City>
		<City>Hailgodonan</City>
		<City>City of Skulls</City>
		<ShortName>Undead</ShortName>
		<LeaderName>Skeleton King</LeaderName>
		<PopulaceName>Constructs</PopulaceName>
		<Alignment>Evil</Alignment>
		<FactionAllegiance>Empire</FactionAllegiance>
		<SelAbilityBonusOption>DominionOfTheDead4</SelAbilityBonusOption>
		<SelAbilityBonusOption>DeathWorship</SelAbilityBonusOption>
		<SelAbilityBonusOption>Rivermod_NoBloodForge</SelAbilityBonusOption>
		<SelAbilityBonusOption>Rivermod_SuperDeathForge</SelAbilityBonusOption>
		<SelAbilityBonusOption>Ability_X_Deorcnysse1000</SelAbilityBonusOption>
		<MusicTheme>WanderersHome</MusicTheme>
		<DefaultCityWallSet>CityWalls_Fence</DefaultCityWallSet>
		<NewCityHubType>CityHub1</NewCityHubType>
		<CapitalHubType>CityHub1</CapitalHubType>
		<RaceClassification>Undead</RaceClassification>
		<RaceDisplayName>Undead</RaceDisplayName>
		<RaceInternalName>Race_Type_Undead</RaceInternalName>
		<GenericUnitType_Male>Generic_Undead_Male</GenericUnitType_Male>
		<GenericUnitType_Female>Generic_Undead_Female</GenericUnitType_Female>
		<TraderUnitType>TraderTest</TraderUnitType>
		<ShopkeeperUnitType>Shopkeeper_Undead</ShopkeeperUnitType>
		<ChooseFactionBack>Faction_Background_Altar.png</ChooseFactionBack>
		<UnitScale>1</UnitScale>
		<UnitSkinColor>0,0,0</UnitSkinColor>
		<UnitHairColor>155,110,75</UnitHairColor>
		<UnitClothing1Color>56,33,13</UnitClothing1Color>
		<UnitClothing2Color>56,33,13</UnitClothing2Color>
		<UnitMetalColor>56,33,13</UnitMetalColor>
		<BuildingPrimaryColor>0,0,0</BuildingPrimaryColor>
		<BuildingSecondaryColor>0,0,0</BuildingSecondaryColor>
		<BuildingRoofColor>0,0,0</BuildingRoofColor>
		<ZoneOfControlColor>0,0,0</ZoneOfControlColor>
		<BuildingStyle>EmpireStyle</BuildingStyle>
		<TechTree>TechTree_X_Undead</TechTree>
		<EnvironmentTerrainType>1</EnvironmentTerrainType>
		<NonBuildableEnvironmentType>GrasslandEnvironment</NonBuildableEnvironmentType>
		<PreferredLogoType>undeadlogo</PreferredLogoType>
		<SovereignUnitType>Sovereign_SkeletonKing</SovereignUnitType>
	</RaceConfig>
</RaceConfigs>
