<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Container>
  <RaceType InternalName="Race_Type_DeathLegion">
    <DisplayName>Chaos Legion</DisplayName>
    <RaceClassification>DeathLegion</RaceClassification>
    <UnitScale>1</UnitScale>
    <UnitSkinColor>20,0,0</UnitSkinColor>
    <UnitHairColor>155,110,75</UnitHairColor>
    <MaleUnitType>Generic_Sovereign_DeathLegion_Male</MaleUnitType>
    <FemaleUnitType>Generic_Sovereign_DeathLegion_Female</FemaleUnitType>
    <GenericUnitType_Male>Generic_DeathLegion_Male</GenericUnitType_Male>
    <GenericUnitType_Female>Generic_DeathLegion_Female</GenericUnitType_Female>
    <TraderUnitType>TraderTest</TraderUnitType>
<StartingUnitType>Unit_Archer_DeathLegion</StartingUnitType>
<StartingUnitType>Unit_Archer_DeathLegion_AI</StartingUnitType>
<StartingUnitType>Unit_Crossbowman_DeathLegion</StartingUnitType>
<StartingUnitType>Unit_Defender_DeathLegion</StartingUnitType>
<StartingUnitType>Unit_Defender_DeathLegion_AI</StartingUnitType>
<StartingUnitType>Unit_Heavy_DeathLegion</StartingUnitType>
<StartingUnitType>Unit_Horseman_DeathLegion</StartingUnitType>
<StartingUnitType>Unit_Light_DeathLegion</StartingUnitType>
<StartingUnitType>Unit_Mage_DeathLegion</StartingUnitType>
<StartingUnitType>Unit_Magic_Heavy_DeathLegion</StartingUnitType>
<StartingUnitType>Unit_Magic_Light_DeathLegion_AI</StartingUnitType>
<StartingUnitType>Unit_Magic_Medium_DeathLegion</StartingUnitType>
<StartingUnitType>Unit_Magic_Medium_DeathLegion_AI</StartingUnitType>
<StartingUnitType>Unit_Medium_DeathLegion</StartingUnitType>
<StartingUnitType>Unit_Medium_DeathLegion_AI</StartingUnitType>
<StartingUnitType>Unit_Peasant_DeathLegion</StartingUnitType>
<StartingUnitType>Unit_Pioneer_DeathLegion</StartingUnitType>
<StartingUnitType>Unit_Scout_DeathLegion</StartingUnitType>
<StartingUnitType>Unit_SpearMaiden_DeathLegion</StartingUnitType>
<StartingUnitType>Unit_Spearman_DeathLegion</StartingUnitType>
   	<StartingUnitType>Unit_SpecialMounted_DeathLegion</StartingUnitType>
	<StartingUnitType>Unit_SpecialMounted_DeathLegion_Horseman</StartingUnitType>
	<ShopkeeperUnitType>Shopkeeper_DeathLegion</ShopkeeperUnitType>
	<SageUnitType>Sage_DeathLegion</SageUnitType>
  </RaceType>
  <RaceConfig InternalName="EmpireofDeathLegion">
    <DisplayName>Chaos Legion</DisplayName>
    <Description>The Chaos Legion is a race of demons. They used to inhabit one of the planes of the Dungeon Dimensions but were banished following events leading up to the Cataclysm. Their physical forms are constantly changing, by the harnessed corruption of their home realm bound in their bodies. 

The Dungeon Dimensions are completely alien to how we think of as the Elemental world. It is most easily described by likening it to some sort of hell where many different demon races fight each other back and forth for dominion. Each area is different from the next – one may be a seemingly endless land of black sand where you can see some manner of night sky, another a cave system that leads into larger caves. They all share some traits, however – without fail, each and every one is more like a battlefield than anything else. The Dungeon Dimensions are also profoundly magical and most believe that this is the reason why there is constantly so much violence in them. New powers are endlessly emerging or evolving and older powers seek to control them or avoid being destroyed by them. In some areas, demons are bred like cattle to fight and die in the wars of the demonlords. Thus the Dungeon Dimensions exist in a state of war that drags on forever, only halted by the occasional failed attack or defeat of a race.

The Chaos Legion is the losing side of such a struggle. Emerging as a fighting power around five thousand years ago, they struggled with local powers until they had achieved a patch of land to call their own. Their power was drawn from red powerstones found in the quarries beneath their lands. It turned them into great fighters, highly violent, but also gave them an unquenchable temper and made them prone to rash actions without considering the long-term goals of the race.

Thus, they assumed a position of offense by attacking and butchering the other demon races in nearby lands, until they met their match around 50 years before the Cataclysm. In that time, they initiated what began as a successful siege of a vast fortress controlled by a bordering demonlord. However, the brute force and overwhelming numbers of the Chaos Legion were beaten aside by the massively intelligent demonlord who was defending the fortress. Older than the Chaos Legion itself, the demonlord drew from his experiences of thousands of years on the battlefield and arranged for supply lines to be interrupted and frequent flanking attacks to upset the camps of the Chaos Legion. The strategy proved effective and, faced with an indestructible fortress ahead to halt their violence and being outmaneuvered by flankers in the areas around the fortress, the Chaos Legion found itself in a dangerous situation. After fifty years of sieging the fortress, the Chaos Legion had become more entrenched and dependent on their own defenses to survive, than the fortress they had attempted to destroy. When the defenders of the fortress began a series of attempts to break out, the Chaos Legion lost all faith that they would succeed and decided to break camp.

Thus it was that, at the time of the Cataclysm, the Chaos Legion was in full retreat and being hounded by enemies on all sides swooping in to take advantage of the Chaos Legion's changing fortune. Taking advantage of the needlessly spent resources of the Chaos Legion, their enemies did not stop pursuing them and soon the lands were taken over by various factions. What forces remained began a long walk away from whatever hostile force was most threatening every day but being surrounded by enemies, such a strategy could not succeed.

The exodus came to an end when they reached the gates leading into another dimension. Now facing certain extinction and with no end of enemies in sight, the Chaos Legion hoped to leave the area and restart elsewhere by traveling through the dimension gates. There, all those races who wanted them gone had gathered a great army to defeat them. The leader of the Chaos Legion, dubbed the No-god, used all of his magic to open up the gates, while the magic of the enemies was directed to try to keep them closed. During the final struggle, the external event called the Cataclysm occurred and, perhaps drawn to the powers channeled into the gates, scattered the remains of the Chaos Legion across all of the Dungeon Dimensions. But not all were lost though – a few thousand appeared in the Elemental world.

The Chaos Legion were cut off from an existence they understood and more importantly their leader. At first they thought this new land was soft and easily conquered but quickly changed their minds as their scarcity in numbers, leadership, and supply of red powerstones made them an easy target by raiders. Where they used to depend on brute force and having a great number of soldiers that were expendable, their tactics initially proved ruinous. At the same time, many of the other races banded together against them to rid the world of a demon invasion. 

The Chaos Legion now faces a precarious situation where they must attempt diplomacy, unthinkable in the Dungeon Dimensions where none can be trusted, for them to have a chance at growing in strength again. Fortunately, they lack this thing called "morality" that many other races seem to think is of such great importance. It will be a cold day in Hell before a demon is beaten in a fair fight by a mere man.</Description>
    <LorebookIntroText>TBD</LorebookIntroText>
    <AIPersonality>AI_General</AIPersonality>
    <Capital>Kizabikar</Capital>
    <City>Dunospfitha</City>
    <City>Gamorulku</City>
    <City>Bukzakareb</City>
    <City>Itijamol</City>
    <City>Ecems</City>
    <City>Piklil</City>
    <City>Rsenotsta</City>
    <City>Oprigfera</City>
    <City>Gethor</City>
    <ShortName>Chaos Legion</ShortName>
    <LeaderName>Ceto, the Pillar</LeaderName>
    <PopulaceName>Frost Giants</PopulaceName>
    <Alignment>Evil</Alignment>
    <FactionAllegiance>Empire</FactionAllegiance>
    
    <SelAbilityBonusOption>DeathLegionSlaves</SelAbilityBonusOption>
<SelAbilityBonusOption>DeathLegionTurningMinds</SelAbilityBonusOption>
    

    <SelAbilityBonusOption>FleshBoundTome</SelAbilityBonusOption>

    <SelAbilityBonusOption>DeathLegionLimit</SelAbilityBonusOption>


    <SelAbilityBonusOption>Rivermod_DeathLegion</SelAbilityBonusOption>
    <SelAbilityBonusOption>Rivermod_NoBloodForge</SelAbilityBonusOption>
	<SelAbilityBonusOption>Ability_X_Deorcnysse1000</SelAbilityBonusOption>
    
    <!--<SelAbilityBonusOption>DeathLegionEmpireStrategic</SelAbilityBonusOption>

	 <SelAbilityBonusOption>Earthsworn</SelAbilityBonusOption>

	 <SelAbilityBonusOption>ExcellentMiners</SelAbilityBonusOption>

	 <SelAbilityBonusOption>Heartoftheforge</SelAbilityBonusOption>
	 <SelAbilityBonusOption>SlowMinds</SelAbilityBonusOption>-->
    <MusicTheme>WanderersHome</MusicTheme>
    <DefaultCityWallSet>CityWalls_Fence</DefaultCityWallSet>
    <NewCityHubType>CityHub1</NewCityHubType>
    <CapitalHubType>CityHub1</CapitalHubType>
    <RaceClassification>DeathLegion</RaceClassification>
    <RaceDisplayName>Chaos Legion</RaceDisplayName>
    <RaceInternalName>Race_Type_DeathLegion</RaceInternalName>
    <GenericUnitType_Male>Generic_DeathLegion_Male</GenericUnitType_Male>
    <GenericUnitType_Female>Generic_DeathLegion_Female</GenericUnitType_Female>
    <TraderUnitType>TraderTest</TraderUnitType>
 
    <ShopkeeperUnitType>Shopkeeper_DeathLegion</ShopkeeperUnitType>
    <ChooseFactionBack>Faction_Background_Altar.png</ChooseFactionBack>
    <UnitScale>1</UnitScale>
    <UnitSkinColor>20,0,0</UnitSkinColor>
    <UnitHairColor>155,110,75</UnitHairColor>
    <UnitClothing1Color>120,25,20,255</UnitClothing1Color>
    <UnitClothing2Color>78,60,55,255</UnitClothing2Color>
    <UnitMetalColor>0,0,0,255</UnitMetalColor>
    <BuildingPrimaryColor>0,0,0</BuildingPrimaryColor>
    <BuildingSecondaryColor>35,0,0</BuildingSecondaryColor>
    <BuildingRoofColor>100,100,100</BuildingRoofColor>
    <ZoneOfControlColor>98,0,0</ZoneOfControlColor>
    <BuildingStyle>EmpireStyle</BuildingStyle>
    <TechTree>TechTree_X_Amarian</TechTree>
    <EnvironmentTerrainType>1</EnvironmentTerrainType>
    <NonBuildableEnvironmentType>GrasslandEnvironment</NonBuildableEnvironmentType>
    <PreferredLogoType>KingdomCrest6</PreferredLogoType>
    <SovereignUnitType>Sovereign_Ceto</SovereignUnitType>
  </RaceConfig>
</Container>
