<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Container>
  <RaceType InternalName="Race_Type_Elves">
    <DisplayName>Elves</DisplayName>
    <RaceClassification>Elves</RaceClassification>
    <UnitScale>1.0</UnitScale>
    <UnitSkinColor>215,150,100</UnitSkinColor>
    <UnitHairColor>155,110,75</UnitHairColor>
    <UnitClothing1Color>200,200,200,255</UnitClothing1Color>
    <UnitClothing2Color>100,100,100,255</UnitClothing2Color>
    <MaleUnitType>Generic_Sovereign_Elves_Male</MaleUnitType>
    <FemaleUnitType>Generic_Sovereign_Elves_Female</FemaleUnitType>
    <GenericUnitType_Male>Generic_Elves_Male</GenericUnitType_Male>
    <GenericUnitType_Female>Generic_Elves_Female</GenericUnitType_Female>
    <TraderUnitType>TraderTest</TraderUnitType>
<StartingUnitType>Unit_Archer_Elves</StartingUnitType>
<StartingUnitType>Unit_Archer_Elves_AI</StartingUnitType>
<StartingUnitType>Unit_Crossbowman_Elves</StartingUnitType>
<StartingUnitType>Unit_Defender_Elves</StartingUnitType>
<StartingUnitType>Unit_Defender_Elves_AI</StartingUnitType>
<StartingUnitType>Unit_Heavy_Elves</StartingUnitType>
<StartingUnitType>Unit_Horseman_Elves</StartingUnitType>
<StartingUnitType>Unit_Light_Elves</StartingUnitType>
<StartingUnitType>Unit_Mage_Elves</StartingUnitType>
<StartingUnitType>Unit_Magic_Heavy_Elves</StartingUnitType>
<StartingUnitType>Unit_Magic_Light_Elves_AI</StartingUnitType>
<StartingUnitType>Unit_Magic_Medium_Elves</StartingUnitType>
<StartingUnitType>Unit_Magic_Medium_Elves_AI</StartingUnitType>
<StartingUnitType>Unit_Medium_Elves</StartingUnitType>
<StartingUnitType>Unit_Medium_Elves_AI</StartingUnitType>
<StartingUnitType>Unit_Peasant_Elves</StartingUnitType>
<StartingUnitType>Unit_Pioneer_Elves</StartingUnitType>
<StartingUnitType>Unit_Scout_Elves</StartingUnitType>
<StartingUnitType>Unit_SpearMaiden_Elves</StartingUnitType>
<StartingUnitType>Unit_Spearman_Elves</StartingUnitType>
    <!--<StartingUnitType>Unit_Umberdroth_Rider_Elves</StartingUnitType>-->
    <ShopkeeperUnitType>Shopkeeper_Elves</ShopkeeperUnitType>
    <SageUnitType>Sage_Elves</SageUnitType>
  </RaceType>
  <RaceConfig InternalName="KingdomofElves">
    <DisplayName>Elves</DisplayName>
    <Description>Elves are immortal magicians that subsisted in forests before the Cataclysm. Now they make a grab for power to prevent it happening again.

Elves have existed in the Elemental world even before humanity. They have played practically no part in the history of the world, however. The Elves kept to the forest, where they  lived out their lives surviving on whatever the forests provide for them. On occasion, the Elves banded together to fight off those who wished to destroy their forests  but mostly this resulted in defeat for the Elves, due to their lack of organization or technology. When such encounters did occur, the Elves usually tried to take advantage of the forests, where they would use bows with great accuracy to harass enemies from afar before retreating to safety. Because they are utterly non-aggressive and have little to trade, Elves have been left alone except when they occupy lands of forests to be used up, in which case the Elves have been driven away.
 
As a race, the Elves believed in a fundamental balance and natural order to all living things. They saw themselves as the epitome of evolution, immortal and thus able to live forever but doing so in a society that puts no strain on the lands around them. With little else to occupy their time, they spent great efforts in nurturing their mental abilities. It should come as no surprise, then, that the Elves are true masters of magic that has been refined over thousands of years. 

The Cataclysm was a time of great sorrow for the Elves. Following the Cataclysm, all of the  forests of the world died and no sapling grew for several years after. Although the Elves did not have much difficulty surviving without their source of food, spiritually the death of the forests was devastating to them. They had come to see the forests as their Mother, their Guardian. To see it killed off in an instant was a particularly traumatic experience.

Thus, the Elves who survived the Cataclysm have decided to take a more direct approach in worldly matters. No longer content to leave their fate – or the fate of the forests – in the hands of the other races: the Elves now seek to control all magic in the world. Their ultimate goal is to prevent another Cataclysm and they believe that only through striving for the balance of magic they previously had can this goal be achieved. Elves are, because of this, particularly careful about sharing magical secrets with other races, whom they believe will not use it in a right way. Furthermore, the Elves have started to leave the forests to grow great cities out of stone and wood. While the forests are still worshiped as a deity – their Mother – they recognize that it is not in itself sentient and the Elves have therefore assumed the role of custodian for all the forests of the world. Though, the elven society is not without its own internal struggles. Building cities has created many new comforts for the Elves and while all recognize the necessity to reach for power in the world, some demand that the Elves return to their old ways rather than become weakened culturally by the new benefits of living in cities.</Description>
    <LorebookIntroText>TBD</LorebookIntroText>
    <AIPersonality>AI_General</AIPersonality>
    <Capital>Alfsigr</Capital>
    <City>Algar</City>
    <City>Alberich</City>
    <City>Alfhildr</City>
    <City>Alvar</City>
    <City>Alric</City>
    <City>Siofra</City>
    <City>Elfwood</City>
    <ShortName>Elves</ShortName>

    <PopulaceName>Elves</PopulaceName>
    <Alignment>Good</Alignment>
    <FactionAllegiance>Kingdom</FactionAllegiance>

    <SelAbilityBonusOption>MasterScoutAbility_Elves</SelAbilityBonusOption>
<SelAbilityBonusOption>MasterworkChain</SelAbilityBonusOption>
<SelAbilityBonusOption>Archers</SelAbilityBonusOption>
<SelAbilityBonusOption>Mindworldunity</SelAbilityBonusOption>

<SelAbilityBonusOption>NoDefensivestructures_Elf</SelAbilityBonusOption>
<SelAbilityBonusOption>NoDominion_Elf</SelAbilityBonusOption>

<SelAbilityBonusOption>Carefulmining_Elf</SelAbilityBonusOption>
<SelAbilityBonusOption>Rivermod_Golem2</SelAbilityBonusOption>


<SelAbilityBonusOption>NoDominion_Elf3</SelAbilityBonusOption>
<SelAbilityBonusOption>Ability_X_Deorcnysse1000</SelAbilityBonusOption>
    <MusicTheme>WanderersHome</MusicTheme>
    <DefaultCityWallSet>CPELF_CityWalls_Fence</DefaultCityWallSet>
    <NewCityHubType>CityHub1</NewCityHubType>
    <CapitalHubType>CityHub1</CapitalHubType>
    <RaceClassification>Elves</RaceClassification>
    <RaceDisplayName>Elves</RaceDisplayName>
    <RaceInternalName>Race_Type_Elves</RaceInternalName>
    <GenericUnitType_Male>Generic_Elves_Male</GenericUnitType_Male>
    <GenericUnitType_Female>Generic_Elves_Female</GenericUnitType_Female>
    <TraderUnitType>TraderTest</TraderUnitType>
    <ShopkeeperUnitType>Shopkeeper_Elves</ShopkeeperUnitType>
    <ChooseFactionBack>Faction_Background_Altar.png</ChooseFactionBack>
    <UnitScale>1</UnitScale>
   		<UnitSkinColor>255,194,130</UnitSkinColor>
		<UnitHairColor>205,170,80</UnitHairColor>
		<UnitClothing1Color>62,91,60,255</UnitClothing1Color>
		<UnitClothing2Color>138,95,54,255</UnitClothing2Color>
		<UnitMetalColor>150,155,135,255</UnitMetalColor>

		<BuildingPrimaryColor>176,122,74</BuildingPrimaryColor>
		<BuildingSecondaryColor>79,48,20</BuildingSecondaryColor>
		<BuildingRoofColor>30,84,48</BuildingRoofColor>

		<ZoneOfControlColor>50,100,0</ZoneOfControlColor>
    <BuildingStyle>KingdomStyle</BuildingStyle>
    <TechTree>TechTree_X_Amarian</TechTree>
    <EnvironmentTerrainType>2</EnvironmentTerrainType>
    <NonBuildableEnvironmentType>DeadEnvironment</NonBuildableEnvironmentType>
    <PreferredLogoType>elfcrest</PreferredLogoType>
    <SovereignUnitType>Sovereign_Ceto</SovereignUnitType>
  </RaceConfig>
</Container>
