<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<Container>
	<RaceType InternalName="Race_Type_Drota">
		<DisplayName>Drota</DisplayName>
		<RaceClassification>Drota</RaceClassification>
		<UnitScale>1</UnitScale>
		<UnitSkinColor>66,66,66</UnitSkinColor>
		<UnitHairColor>155,110,75</UnitHairColor>
		<MaleUnitType>Generic_Sovereign_Drota_Male</MaleUnitType>
		<FemaleUnitType>Generic_Sovereign_Drota_Female</FemaleUnitType>
		<GenericUnitType_Male>Generic_Drota_Male</GenericUnitType_Male>
		<GenericUnitType_Female>Generic_Drota_Female</GenericUnitType_Female>
		<TraderUnitType>TraderTest</TraderUnitType>
		<StartingUnitType>Unit_Archer_Drota</StartingUnitType>
		<StartingUnitType>Unit_Archer_Drota_AI</StartingUnitType>
		<StartingUnitType>Unit_Crossbowman_Drota</StartingUnitType>
		<StartingUnitType>Unit_Defender_Drota</StartingUnitType>
		<StartingUnitType>Unit_Defender_Drota_AI</StartingUnitType>
		<StartingUnitType>Unit_Heavy_Drota</StartingUnitType>
		<StartingUnitType>Unit_Horseman_Drota</StartingUnitType>
		<StartingUnitType>Unit_Light_Drota</StartingUnitType>
		<StartingUnitType>Unit_Mage_Drota</StartingUnitType>
		<StartingUnitType>Unit_Magic_Heavy_Drota</StartingUnitType>
		<StartingUnitType>Unit_Magic_Light_Drota_AI</StartingUnitType>
		<StartingUnitType>Unit_Magic_Medium_Drota</StartingUnitType>
		<StartingUnitType>Unit_Magic_Medium_Drota_AI</StartingUnitType>
		<StartingUnitType>Unit_Medium_Drota</StartingUnitType>
		<StartingUnitType>Unit_Medium_Drota_AI</StartingUnitType>
		<StartingUnitType>Unit_Peasant_Drota</StartingUnitType>
		<StartingUnitType>Unit_Pioneer_Drota</StartingUnitType>
		<StartingUnitType>Unit_Scout_Drota</StartingUnitType>
		<StartingUnitType>Unit_SpearMaiden_Drota</StartingUnitType>
		<StartingUnitType>Unit_Spearman_Drota</StartingUnitType>

		<SageUnitType>Sage_Drota</SageUnitType>
		<ShopkeeperUnitType>Shopkeeper_Drota</ShopkeeperUnitType>
	</RaceType>
	<RaceConfig InternalName="EmpireOfDrota">
		<DisplayName>Drota</DisplayName>

		<Description>The Drota became Spider hybrids during the Cataclysm, and are well-known for their desire to hunt all living things.

The Drota is one of the most ancient races – older than even mankind – that is native to the Elemental world. They hunted dragons more than five thousand years ago, and have undergone many shifts in culture. They put a lot of effort into recording and maintaining their history, in particular their successful hunters and their bloodlines.

However, the one thousand years before the Cataclysm mostly saw the Drota killed off due to their tribal structure and insistence on "hunting" all the other races of the world. The Drota are at heart hunters and by far the best hunters in the world. This was deeply ingrained in their hierarchies, with the best hunter also leading the tribe. A tribal leader that did not lead the tribe on constant hunts was thrown out. Because of this reason, diplomatic relations with the Drota have always failed within a few years. Indeed, it is difficult to negotiate deals with an entity that almost constantly smiles at you and tells you how he's going to "hunt you down". The century before the Cataclysm, the Drota were almost completely conquered by the other races and was more considered a pest, performing the occasional raid on the countryside rather than any true danger to civilization. This was also enforced due to their inability to use the magic in the shards – the coming of the Titans and their gathering all magic into the shards meant that the Drota's ancient magic was turned powerless over the course of  a few weeks.

70 years before the Cataclysm, a new leader emerged, dubbed the Stormlord by the Drota. She was the first Drota to manage channeling from the Shards. The Drota tell of how the Stormlord made a deal with some extraterrestrial being, where she traded her "little brother" (an organ that grants the Drota great regenerative abilities) for the ability to channel magic again. The Stormlord then used her power to lead her spider cult to dominion over all the Drota tribes. This ensured the Drota were once again a threat to all other races just before the Cataclysm. 

But not even the Drota could imagine what would happen during the Cataclysm. Even to this day there are many who will tell the story differently. What is known with certainty is this – before the Cataclysm, the Drota were humanoids like any other, with two legs, arms, and a head. After the Cataclysm, the Stormlord and her closest followers had turned into a hybrid between spider and Drota – the upper body remained intact, but the lower body had been replaced by the body of a spider, only with six legs instead of eight. 

Some say the Stormlord was granted this great boon for her loyal worshiping of some obscure spider god. Others say the Cataclysm merely happened while the Stormlord was in the act of performing some unholy union between spider and Drota and the great surge in magic caused the hybrids to form.

The century after the Cataclysm saw a civil war amongst the Drota, where the spider cult eventually enslaved all other Drota and forced them to bear hybrid children. Their new hybrid bodies granted them greatly enhanced abilities that assisted them in the various hunts performed. The Drota are now a very different species compared to that which existed before the Cataclysm. Their military power is mostly untested against other races but it seems clear from early contact with the Drota that their cultural preference for war and "hunting" remains. 
		</Description>
		<LorebookIntroText>TBD</LorebookIntroText>
		<AIPersonality>AI_General</AIPersonality>
		<Capital>Quathari</Capital>
		<City>Ashsh</City>
		<City>Laerd</City>
		<City>Adch</City>
		<City>Etani</City>
		<City>Whaych</City>
		<City>Eyre</City>
		<City>Keild</City>
		<City>Nult</City>
		<City>Imr</City>
		<ShortName>Drotas</ShortName>
		<LeaderName>Ceto, the Pillar</LeaderName>
		<PopulaceName>Constructs</PopulaceName>
		<Alignment>Evil</Alignment>
		<FactionAllegiance>Empire</FactionAllegiance>
		<SelAbilityBonusOption>DrotaEmpireTactical</SelAbilityBonusOption>
		<SelAbilityBonusOption>DrotaEmpireTactical2</SelAbilityBonusOption>
		<SelAbilityBonusOption>DrotaEmpireTactical4</SelAbilityBonusOption>
		<!--<SelAbilityBonusOption>DrotaEmpireTactical5</SelAbilityBonusOption>-->
		<SelAbilityBonusOption>DrotaEmpireTactical6</SelAbilityBonusOption>
		<SelAbilityBonusOption>MasterworkChain</SelAbilityBonusOption>
		<SelAbilityBonusOption>Rivermod_Drota</SelAbilityBonusOption>
		<SelAbilityBonusOption>MasterScout_Drota</SelAbilityBonusOption>
		<SelAbilityBonusOption>CultofaHundredEyes</SelAbilityBonusOption>
		<SelAbilityBonusOption>Ability_X_Deorcnysse1000</SelAbilityBonusOption>
		<!--	 <SelAbilityBonusOption>DrotaMagicians</SelAbilityBonusOption>
		<SelAbilityBonusOption>Heartoftheforge</SelAbilityBonusOption>
		<SelAbilityBonusOption>SlowMinds</SelAbilityBonusOption>-->
		<MusicTheme>WanderersHome</MusicTheme>
		<DefaultCityWallSet>CityWalls_Fence</DefaultCityWallSet>
		<NewCityHubType>CityHub1</NewCityHubType>
		<CapitalHubType>CityHub1</CapitalHubType>
		<RaceClassification>Drota</RaceClassification>
		<RaceDisplayName>Living Stone</RaceDisplayName>
		<RaceInternalName>Race_Type_Drota</RaceInternalName>
		<GenericUnitType_Male>Generic_Drota_Male</GenericUnitType_Male>
		<GenericUnitType_Female>Generic_Drota_Female</GenericUnitType_Female>
		<TraderUnitType>TraderTest</TraderUnitType>
		<ShopkeeperUnitType>Shopkeeper_Drota</ShopkeeperUnitType>
		<ChooseFactionBack>Faction_Background_Altar.png</ChooseFactionBack>
		<UnitScale>1</UnitScale>
		<UnitSkinColor>66,66,66</UnitSkinColor>
		<UnitHairColor>155,110,75</UnitHairColor>
		<UnitClothing1Color>120,25,20,255</UnitClothing1Color>
		<UnitClothing2Color>78,60,55,255</UnitClothing2Color>
		<UnitMetalColor>255,255,255</UnitMetalColor>
		<BuildingPrimaryColor>100,100,100</BuildingPrimaryColor>
		<BuildingSecondaryColor>100,100,100</BuildingSecondaryColor>
		<BuildingRoofColor>100,100,100</BuildingRoofColor>
		<ZoneOfControlColor>200,70,0</ZoneOfControlColor>
		<BuildingStyle>EmpireStyle</BuildingStyle>
		<TechTree>TechTree_X_Amarian</TechTree>
		<EnvironmentTerrainType>1</EnvironmentTerrainType>
		<NonBuildableEnvironmentType>GrasslandEnvironment</NonBuildableEnvironmentType>
		<PreferredLogoType>GenericCrest40</PreferredLogoType>
		<SovereignUnitType>Sovereign_Ceto</SovereignUnitType>
	</RaceConfig>
</Container>
