<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Container>
	<RaceType InternalName="Race_Type_FrostGiants">
		<DisplayName>Frost Giant</DisplayName>
		<RaceClassification>FrostGiants</RaceClassification>
		<UnitScale>1</UnitScale>
		<UnitSkinColor>200,200,200</UnitSkinColor>
		<UnitHairColor>155,110,75</UnitHairColor>
		<MaleUnitType>Generic_Sovereign_FrostGiants_Male</MaleUnitType>
		<FemaleUnitType>Generic_Sovereign_FrostGiants_Female</FemaleUnitType>
		<GenericUnitType_Male>Generic_FrostGiants_Male</GenericUnitType_Male>
		<GenericUnitType_Female>Generic_FrostGiants_Female</GenericUnitType_Female>
		<TraderUnitType>TraderTest</TraderUnitType>
		<StartingUnitType>Unit_Archer_FrostGiants</StartingUnitType>
		<StartingUnitType>Unit_Archer_FrostGiants_AI</StartingUnitType>
		<StartingUnitType>Unit_Crossbowman_FrostGiants</StartingUnitType>
		<StartingUnitType>Unit_Defender_FrostGiants</StartingUnitType>
		<StartingUnitType>Unit_Defender_FrostGiants_AI</StartingUnitType>
		<StartingUnitType>Unit_Heavy_FrostGiants</StartingUnitType>
		<StartingUnitType>Unit_Horseman_FrostGiants</StartingUnitType>
		<StartingUnitType>Unit_Light_FrostGiants</StartingUnitType>
		<StartingUnitType>Unit_Mage_FrostGiants</StartingUnitType>
		<StartingUnitType>Unit_Magic_Heavy_FrostGiants</StartingUnitType>
		<StartingUnitType>Unit_Magic_Light_FrostGiants_AI</StartingUnitType>
		<StartingUnitType>Unit_Magic_Medium_FrostGiants</StartingUnitType>
		<StartingUnitType>Unit_Magic_Medium_FrostGiants_AI</StartingUnitType>
		<StartingUnitType>Unit_Medium_FrostGiants</StartingUnitType>
		<StartingUnitType>Unit_Medium_FrostGiants_AI</StartingUnitType>
		<StartingUnitType>Unit_Peasant_FrostGiants</StartingUnitType>
		<StartingUnitType>Unit_Pioneer_FrostGiants</StartingUnitType>
		<StartingUnitType>Unit_Scout_FrostGiants</StartingUnitType>
		<StartingUnitType>Unit_SpearMaiden_FrostGiants</StartingUnitType>
		<StartingUnitType>Unit_Spearman_FrostGiants</StartingUnitType>
		<SageUnitType>Sage_FrostGiants</SageUnitType>

	</RaceType>
	<RaceConfig InternalName="EmpireofFrostGiants">
		<DisplayName>Frost Giants</DisplayName>
		<Description>From a land of cold and darkness come the Frost Giants. Huge beings of immense powers, they represent military might the like of which has never been seen on Elemental before.

The Frost Giants have always been a nagging presence in the world of Elemental. Before the Cataclysm, they inhabited a great continent north of the world that was permanently covered in ice. Perhaps this is why you'll rarely find a hint of their existence in the history books made by the Human races. The Frost Giants kept to themselves and were content to stay inside the environment they preferred. Concurrently, they had nothing to offer in trade or resources and thus were left alone by the free merchants. 

Forced to conserve energy, Frost Giants regularly went into hibernation during the coldest months of the years but it was not uncommon for this hibernation to last several years for some. This and the fact that the Frost Giants lacked any real hierarchy meant that other diplomatic relations were difficult to maintain and eventually all contact broke down, condemned as pointless. 

The Frost Giants possess an unnatural ability to somehow draw energy from being cold. This is what allowed them to survive in a land covered in snow all year around. They lived in small tribes with few connections to others, except young males that would always leave their tribe and join another when entering adulthood. They possessed little in terms of culture and they had only a few tools made out of stones and twinned hair.

During the Cataclysm, the entire continent of the Frost Giants sank beneath the oceans. A few Frost Giants were able to survive by climbing aboard icebergs that they then willed south by magic. 

The Frost Giants arrived at the beaches of the Elemental continent and quickly established themselves as a power to be reckoned with. Although not clear from before the Cataclysm, the Frost Giants live exceptionally long lives, and only continue to grow as they do so. Thus, a Frost Giant army can vary greatly in power, regardless of how many they actually bring to the fight. The youngest are not much taller than any men, while the oldest can stand thrice as tall as the tallest man. Their giant physique makes fighting them very difficult, as they are so unlike any other race in size and power. 

The Cataclysm has been a significant event in Frost Giant history. They had little culture before the Cataclysm but they did love their land and now blame the other races in the world for causing the utter annihilation of their continent. The Frost Giants primarily seek vengeance on all of the magicians in the Elemental world, whom they blame for the Cataclysm, even if none were alive back then (it is, as they call it, the "inherited sin" of the "worldbreakers"). The Frost Giants also seek to turn this continent into a new homeland by covering all the world in eternal snow. 

Another recent change in Frost Giant society is the elevation of their channelers. Before those were scorned for their lack of physical prowess but not even the dumbest Frost Giant can deny that it was only thanks to their channelers, who steered the icebergs south when their continent sank, that the Frost Giants are even alive today. Others are also beginning to take notice of the massive difference in mental capacity between a normal Frost Giant and a channeler. Hence, the channelers have been given an honorary status at the very top of the hierarchy, above the oldest of warriors.
		</Description>
		<LorebookIntroText>TBD</LorebookIntroText>
		<AIPersonality>AI_General</AIPersonality>
		<Capital>Jotunheim</Capital>
		<City>Hel</City>
		<City>Reynes</City>
		<City>Agartha</City>
		<City>Lemuria</City>
		<City>Nyrsa</City>
		<City>Thule</City>
		<City>Ys</City>
		<City>Kvenland</City>
		<ShortName>Frost Giants</ShortName>
		<LeaderName>Ceto, the Pillar</LeaderName>
		<PopulaceName>Frost Giants</PopulaceName>
		<Alignment>Evil</Alignment>
		<FactionAllegiance>Empire</FactionAllegiance>
		<SelAbilityBonusOption>FrostgiantEmpireTactical2</SelAbilityBonusOption>
		<SelAbilityBonusOption>FrostgiantEmpireTactical3</SelAbilityBonusOption>
		<SelAbilityBonusOption>MasterScout_FG</SelAbilityBonusOption>
		<!--<SelAbilityBonusOption>DrotaEmpireTactical3</SelAbilityBonusOption>-->
		<SelAbilityBonusOption>FrostGiant_Nocountryforoldgiants</SelAbilityBonusOption>
		<SelAbilityBonusOption>FrostgiantEmpireTactical4</SelAbilityBonusOption>
		<SelAbilityBonusOption>FrostGiant_Frostfire</SelAbilityBonusOption>
		<SelAbilityBonusOption>FrostGiant_AlienWorld</SelAbilityBonusOption>
		<SelAbilityBonusOption>Rivermod_blockmagmaforge</SelAbilityBonusOption>
		<SelAbilityBonusOption>Ability_X_Deorcnysse1000</SelAbilityBonusOption>
		<MusicTheme>WanderersHome</MusicTheme>
		<DefaultCityWallSet>CityWalls_Fence</DefaultCityWallSet>
		<NewCityHubType>CityHub1</NewCityHubType>
		<CapitalHubType>CityHub1</CapitalHubType>
		<RaceClassification>FrostGiants</RaceClassification>
		<RaceDisplayName>Living Stone</RaceDisplayName>
		<RaceInternalName>Race_Type_FrostGiants</RaceInternalName>
		<GenericUnitType_Male>Generic_FrostGiants_Male</GenericUnitType_Male>
		<GenericUnitType_Female>Generic_FrostGiants_Female</GenericUnitType_Female>
		<TraderUnitType>TraderTest</TraderUnitType>
		<ShopkeeperUnitType>Shopkeeper_FrostGiants</ShopkeeperUnitType>
		<ChooseFactionBack>Faction_Background_Altar.png</ChooseFactionBack>
		<UnitScale>1</UnitScale>
		<UnitSkinColor>255,255,255</UnitSkinColor>
		<UnitHairColor>255,255,255</UnitHairColor>
		<UnitClothing1Color>130,165,190</UnitClothing1Color>
		<UnitClothing2Color>130,165,190</UnitClothing2Color>
		<UnitMetalColor>130,165,190</UnitMetalColor>
		<BuildingPrimaryColor>165,145,130</BuildingPrimaryColor>
		<BuildingSecondaryColor>75,60,50</BuildingSecondaryColor>
		<BuildingRoofColor>90,15,10</BuildingRoofColor>
		<ZoneOfControlColor>50,50,250</ZoneOfControlColor>
		<BuildingStyle>EmpireStyle</BuildingStyle>
		<TechTree>TechTree_X_Amarian</TechTree>
		<EnvironmentTerrainType>1</EnvironmentTerrainType>
		<NonBuildableEnvironmentType>GrasslandEnvironment</NonBuildableEnvironmentType>
		<PreferredLogoType>frostgiantlogo</PreferredLogoType>
		<SovereignUnitType>Sovereign_Ceto</SovereignUnitType>
	</RaceConfig>
</Container>
